<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Discover Advanced</title>
  
  <subtitle>Enjoy life easier but more creative!</subtitle>
  <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/"/>
  <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.908Z</updated>
  <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Charles</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Understanding LIBOR Changeover with Artificial Intelligence: Perspectives by ABBYY Experts</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/understanding-libor-changeover-with-artificial-intelligence-perspectives-by-abbyy-experts/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/understanding-libor-changeover-with-artificial-intelligence-perspectives-by-abbyy-experts/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.908Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.908Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Understanding-LIBOR-Changeover-with-Artificial-Intelligence-Perspectives-by-ABBYY-Experts"><a href="#Understanding-LIBOR-Changeover-with-Artificial-Intelligence-Perspectives-by-ABBYY-Experts" class="headerlink" title="Understanding LIBOR Changeover with Artificial Intelligence: Perspectives by ABBYY Experts"></a>Understanding LIBOR Changeover with Artificial Intelligence: Perspectives by ABBYY Experts</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h1 id="Why-AI-Matters-in-LIBOR-Transition"><a href="#Why-AI-Matters-in-LIBOR-Transition" class="headerlink" title="Why AI Matters in LIBOR Transition"></a>Why AI Matters in LIBOR Transition</h1><h6 id="Reginald-J-Twigg"><a href="#Reginald-J-Twigg" class="headerlink" title="Reginald J. Twigg"></a>Reginald J. Twigg</h6><p>July 15, 2020</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/28993/11986_cover_848x444.png"                      alt="Why AI Matters in LIBOR Transition | ABBYY Blog Post"                > </p><p>On July 27, 2017, the UK’s Financial Conduct Authority announced that the London Interbank Offered Rate (LIBOR), one of the world’s most widely used interest rate benchmarks, will be phased out by the end of 2021.</p><p>While officially a UK protocol, LIBOR is used as a reference rate by financial institutions around the world, including the United States, and its impending demise has generated calls to action across the global banking and finance industry. The US Federal Housing Finance Agency, to cite just one example, has <a class="link"   href="https://www.fhfa.gov/SupervisionRegulation/LIBORTransition" >announced a comprehensive LIBOR transition plan <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> for Fannie Mae, Freddie Mac, and the Federal Home Loan Banks.</p><p>You may ask how such a seemingly little change in a bank protocol can be turning the industry upside down, creating panic and tens of billions of dollars in reviewing contracts and looking for solutions for remediation. The answer is simpler than meets the eye – its because contract language (the place where LIBOR is coded into the business of banking) has become hard-coded in all practices of setting lending rates across all banks doing business with the UK and US.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/28997/11986_picture_2_848x444.png"                      alt="Why AI Matters in LIBOR Transition"                ></p><p>Combing through this Mt Everest of documents would require armies of trained legal specialists, attorneys, and regulators at a cost of time and money simply impossible to fathom. Oliver Wyman estimates that fourteen of the world’s top banks will pay $1.2B in remediation, while the costs for the industry as a whole will be multiples of that sum. ‘Much of this cost,’ he estimates ‘is linked to the arduous task of changing the terms of contracts tied to Libor whose duration extend beyond the 2021 deadline.’ i</p><h2 id="If-ever-there-was-a-use-case-for-AI-with-ML"><a href="#If-ever-there-was-a-use-case-for-AI-with-ML" class="headerlink" title="If ever there was a use case for AI with ML"></a>If ever there was a use case for AI with ML</h2><p>So let’s talk a minute about contract language and how it is holding the banking industry hostage – the trillion dollar question - why consultants are needed and why technology is so important in remediation, and, in particular, why Artificial Intelligence (AI) with Machine Learning (ML) can make its biggest difference as a solution. The answer is simple, even if the solution is sophisticated. LIBOR is embedded in tens of thousands of contracts and agreements by which banks do business with each other, client businesses, and government regulators.</p><p>AI with ML has been much hyped in recent years, but it often sounds like a solution looking for a problem. AI, in simple terms, is building computer programs (also called ‘computer vision’) to help them find, interpret, make decisions, and take action on complex language embedded in a corpus of data or documents as expert or highly-trained users would. Far from being a replacement for high-paid skilled labor, such as attorneys, paralegals, analysts and consultants, AI with ML helps them scale to global challenges such as LIBOR phase out.</p><h2 id="Named-entity-recognition-extraction-has-advanced"><a href="#Named-entity-recognition-extraction-has-advanced" class="headerlink" title="Named entity recognition &amp; extraction has advanced"></a>Named entity recognition &amp; extraction has advanced</h2><p>A particularly useful application of AI for LIBOR transition is recent advancements in <strong>named entity extraction</strong>, whereby AI-based programs can learn how to recognize legal entities in the corpus of contracts and related documents. An entity is a specific person, place, and&#x2F;or action that is composed of multiple data fields that can be found anywhere in a contract. Often implied and never in a predictable place, named entities can be particularly vexing for legal experts to find as they plow through mountains of contracts.</p><p>LIBOR rates, clauses, and affected parties are all entities in contracts that are rarely expressed in the same way within a single contract, let alone a single bank’s thousands of such contracts. But AI with machine learning can learn all of the permutations of these entities, including all of the stated and implied references to such entities, but can identify and understand them in seconds on a machine while a legal expert could take an hour or more to perform the same review. But AI does not get tired or distracted, like humans can, and can deliver results more consistently across thousands of documents.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/28998/11986_picture_848x444.png"                      alt="Why AI Matters in LIBOR Transition"                ></p><p>With recent advancements in named entity recognition and extraction techniques, such as the ability of data scientists and legal experts to train the software with comprehensive taxonomies and variations (thesaurus, legal codes, aliases), modern AI solutions can be in production in a matter of days or weeks at a fraction of the cost of hiring an army of consultants and legal teams to do the work. LIBOR remediation experts can now help train their ‘virtual legal team’ of AI&#x2F;ML software and supporting RPA bots to be their army of expert assistants to find, remediate, or flag for additional review all the impacted contracts and legal business entities.</p><p>Here is where AI with ML can shine as an expert solution for LIBOR transition. By supplementing and learning how to work as an army of virtual assistants, a specialized named entity recognition solution, powered by modern AL with ML, can reduce the time of locating, understanding, and remediating the sheer volume of LIBOR-related documents from tens of person years to weeks or months of computer time. The payback in risk abatement, time, and money can speak for itself.</p><p>Watch for our webinar, <a href="https://info.bai.org/mitigating-risk-from-libor-contracts-webinar.html?utm_medium=email&utm_source=marketing_ref&utm_campaign=webinar_091720&utm_content=ABBYYY"><strong>Mitigating risk from LIBOR contracts</strong></a>, to see a demo of how AI technologies can be deployed to identify and remediate LIBOR contracts, to monitor and audit processes, and to gain key takeaways on how to lead your LIBOR transformation initiatives.</p><hr><p>i <em>Sinead Cruise, Lawrence White, ‘The End of LIBOR: The Biggest Banking Challenge You’ve Ever Heard Of,’ Reuters 8 October, 2019.</em></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/artificial-intelligence-ai/"  title="Artificial Intelligence (AI)">Artificial Intelligence (AI) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Financial Services <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Legal <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25636/02c-reggietwigg-99x99.png"                      alt="Reggie Twigg ABBYY"                ></p><p>Reginald J. Twigg</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2082526/7443" target="_top" id="2082526"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2082526"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2082526/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Understanding-LIBOR-Changeover-with-Artificial-Intelligence-Perspectives-by-ABBYY-Experts&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Understanding-LIBOR-Changeover-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Essentials of Process Mining: How It Transforms Data Into Actionable Insights for Organizations</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/the-essentials-of-process-mining-how-it-transforms-data-into-actionable-insights-for-organizations/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/the-essentials-of-process-mining-how-it-transforms-data-into-actionable-insights-for-organizations/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.897Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.897Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="The-Essentials-of-Process-Mining-How-It-Transforms-Data-Into-Actionable-Insights-for-Organizations"><a href="#The-Essentials-of-Process-Mining-How-It-Transforms-Data-Into-Actionable-Insights-for-Organizations" class="headerlink" title="The Essentials of Process Mining: How It Transforms Data Into Actionable Insights for Organizations"></a>The Essentials of Process Mining: How It Transforms Data Into Actionable Insights for Organizations</h2><p>Data sheet</p><h2 id="What-Is-Process-Mining-and-Why-Do-You-Need-It"><a href="#What-Is-Process-Mining-and-Why-Do-You-Need-It" class="headerlink" title="What Is Process Mining, and Why Do You Need It?"></a>What Is Process Mining, and Why Do You Need It?</h2><h3 id="Find-out-what’s-working-well-and-what-needs-improvement"><a href="#Find-out-what’s-working-well-and-what-needs-improvement" class="headerlink" title="Find out what’s working well, and what needs improvement"></a>Find out what’s working well, and what needs improvement</h3><p>In today’s changing business environment, continuous process improvement is a must. To remain profitable and competitive, there’s simply no room for inefficiencies. That’s why so many leaders are turning to process mining. It’s an approach to process improvement that enables you to make in-the-moment decisions based on fact rather than emotions. We created this infobook to help you understand how process mining works, how it benefits businesses, and how to implement it successfully.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://purchase.swifdoo.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=40002162&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/8b932759a5a04ddb34bf79e3f9072e4b/products/1_Product%20box%20white-1024x1024.png"                      border="0"                >SwifDoo PDF Perpetual (1 PC) Free upgrade. No monthly fees ever.<br></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Download-it-now"><a href="#Download-it-now" class="headerlink" title="Download it now!"></a>Download it now!</h3><p>Download it now to learn about these five key reasons that businesses invest in process mining (plus three tips for implementing it successfully):</p><ul><li>To gain objective visibility into their operations</li><li>To make decisions based on facts, not emotions</li><li>To derive maximum value from data</li><li>To drive a culture of continuous improvement</li><li>To improve customer experiences</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=37701530&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/6fe0c81e3f9438db11ebbfba6c5ce460/products/copy_cbLogo_with_text_blue.png"                      border="0"                >CalendarBudget - Monthly subscription membership to CalendarBudget via web browser or mobile app. Support included. </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Thank-you-for-your-interest-in-ABBYY-and-its-technologies"><a href="#Thank-you-for-your-interest-in-ABBYY-and-its-technologies" class="headerlink" title="Thank you for your interest in ABBYY and its technologies."></a>Thank you for your interest in ABBYY and its technologies.</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://digital.abbyy.com/hubfs/documents/content/datasheet-processintelligence-process-mining-en.pdf"  title="Read data sheet">Read data sheet <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=38729081&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://website-prod.cache.wpscdn.com/img/wps-writer-free-word-processor-1x.3d9c80d.png"                      border="0"                ><br>WPS Office Premium ( File Recovery, Photo Scanning, Convert PDF)–Yearly</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY"><a href="#Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Have questions? Contact ABBYY"></a>Have questions? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form"><a href="#Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form" class="headerlink" title="Get your copy by filling in the form."></a>Get your copy by filling in the form.</h4><p>First name*</p><p>Last name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Salutation</p><p>Academic Title</p><p>Query string</p><p>Add your question or describe your interest</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>City</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;The-Essentials-of-Process-Mining-How-It-Transforms-Data-Into-Actionable-Insights-for-Organizations&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#The-Essentials-of-Proc</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Southampton University Digitizes Massive Print Collections, Enhancing Accessibility for Students and Researchers</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/southampton-university-digitizes-massive-print-collections-enhancing-accessibility-for-students-and-researchers/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/southampton-university-digitizes-massive-print-collections-enhancing-accessibility-for-students-and-researchers/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.890Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.890Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Southampton-University-Digitizes-Massive-Print-Collections-Enhancing-Accessibility-for-Students-and-Researchers"><a href="#Southampton-University-Digitizes-Massive-Print-Collections-Enhancing-Accessibility-for-Students-and-Researchers" class="headerlink" title="Southampton University Digitizes Massive Print Collections, Enhancing Accessibility for Students and Researchers"></a>Southampton University Digitizes Massive Print Collections, Enhancing Accessibility for Students and Researchers</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Retourner aux expériences clients <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Education&#x2F;Research</p><h2 id="L’universite-de-Southampton-ameliore-l’acces-a-sa-collection-en-numerisant-de-volumineuses-quantites-de-documents-imprimes"><a href="#L’universite-de-Southampton-ameliore-l’acces-a-sa-collection-en-numerisant-de-volumineuses-quantites-de-documents-imprimes" class="headerlink" title="L’université de Southampton améliore l’accès à sa collection en numérisant de volumineuses quantités de documents imprimés"></a>L’université de Southampton améliore l’accès à sa collection en numérisant de volumineuses quantités de documents imprimés</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/fr/39653.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Retourner aux expériences clients <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="L’universite-de-Southampton-ameliore-l’acces-a-sa-collection-en-numerisant-de-volumineuses-quantites-de-documents-imprimes-1"><a href="#L’universite-de-Southampton-ameliore-l’acces-a-sa-collection-en-numerisant-de-volumineuses-quantites-de-documents-imprimes-1" class="headerlink" title="L’université de Southampton améliore l’accès à sa collection en numérisant de volumineuses quantités de documents imprimés"></a>L’université de Southampton améliore l’accès à sa collection en numérisant de volumineuses quantités de documents imprimés</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/10189/cs-unisouthampton-rs-f.pdf" >Afficher ou télécharger une version imprimable de cet article (PDF 329 kb) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://twopages.pxf.io/c/5597632/1873305/18544" target="_top" id="1873305"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18544-1873305"                      border="0" alt="" width="1080" height="1350"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1873305/18544"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Contexte"><a href="#Contexte" class="headerlink" title="Contexte"></a>Contexte</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"                                     >La bibliothèque de l’université de Southampton accueille environ 35 000 étudiants et membres de son personnel. Elle offre un accès à une très vaste collection de qualité supérieure : 1,5 millions de livres et plusieurs millions de pages de documents d’archive. La bibliothèque s’est récemment lancée dans un programme de numérisation d’un nombre important de textes clés via l’Unité de numérisation de bibliothèques (LDU, Library Digitisation Unit). La LDU est une opération phare dans le secteur de l’éducation et se spécialise dans la capture numérique d’un large éventail de documents pour les référentiels ou la distribution sur Internet via des liens du catalogue de la bibliothèque. La démarche de la bibliothèque universitaire consiste à offrir un accès complet aux documents numériques qu’elle crée, chaque fois que cela est possible et autorisé.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4727541&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/5f4f7141b65a730b4efb0e0d51f63e94/products/copy_copy_forexrobotronbox.gif"                      border="0"                >Forex Robotron Gold Package</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p>ABBYY FineReader, un produit logiciel conçu pour la numérisation et la numérisation ad-hoc, a été utilisé par la bibliothèque pendant un certain nombre d’années pour numériser une petite quantité de pages, et occasionnellement l’intégralité de livres. Ce programme est aussi utilisé pour la reconnaissance de texte et la reconnaissance optique de caractères (OCR, optical character recognition). La bibliothèque s’est rapidement rendue compte que pour automatiser le processus OCR, avec un rendement élevé, et atteindre son objectif, qui est de numériser un demi-million de pages par an, elle aurait besoin d’un produit plus robuste et capable de traiter automatiquement d’importants volumes de documents.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.mondly.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=ATISTUDI&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mondly.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3D%2BEducational%2B970x90%2B"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/69c418c33ec2e1a4267fa9bb77fa1428/educational-970x90.gif"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Solution"><a href="#Solution" class="headerlink" title="Solution"></a>Solution</h2><p>Pour trouver une solution permettant de traiter les documents imprimés, de les convertir en formats interrogeables, tels que le PDF et le PDF&#x2F;A, et de numériser la création d’archives ou de dossiers, la bibliothèque a examiné diverses options disponibles sur le marché. Les critères suivants ont été examinés pour un certain nombre de produits: rapidité et qualité de l’OCR, gamme de formats et de compressions à l’exportation et possibilité d’intégrer des API&#x2F;workflows. Après avoir examiné un certain nombre de produits, la bibliothèque a sélectionné ABBYY Recognition Server comme solution la plus performante.</p><p>La bibliothèque a choisi Recognition Server car ce logiciel répondait parfaitement à ses attentes: mise à disposition d’une reconnaissance de grande qualité pour les textes imprimés, un large éventail d’options d’exportation et une API ouverte permettant d’intégrer facilement d’autres programmes. La bibliothèque souhaitait intégrer Recognition Server au logiciel de workflow Goobi, développé par Intranda GmbH, de la LDU. Le logiciel de workflow de production Goobi est une application Internet qui gère et effectue un suivi des projets de numérisation de bibliothèques. Le niveau de qualité du service après-vente et une maintenance abordable ont été des atouts supplémentaires en faveur d’ABBYY.</p><p>La LDU utilise actuellement jusqu’à six scanners de livres et un scanner en ligne haut de gamme pour numériser les textes et les images faisant partie de sa collection. L’API Tickets XML d’ABBYY Recognition Server a été utilisée pour l’intégration à Goobi Workflow. Une fois les documents imprimés numérisés, Goobi gère la mise en attente de tâches Recognition Server puis contrôle les résultats. La production coordonnée de caractères peut être intégrée à une couche de présentationpour l’indexation et l’accès. Par conséquent, dès que l’utilisateur du scanner termine la numérisation d’un livre, les fichiers sont automatiquement déplacés vers chaque étape du workflow. Deux des plus importants programmes de numérisation du stock de la bibliothèque de l’université de Southampton comprenaient les projets financés par le Comité commun des systèmes d’information (JISC, Joint Information Systems Committee). Le JISC s’inspire des établissements d’enseignement supérieur et des universités du Royaume-Uni qui utilisent des technologies numériques de manière innovante et permet au Royaume-Uni de conserver sa position de leader mondial dans le secteur de l’éducation. Ces deux projets ont chacun généré plus d’un million d’images numériques:</p><p><strong>Numérisation des documents papier du Parlement datant du 18ème siècle:</strong> ceci comprend les journaux de la chambre des Lords et de la chambre des Communes, les registres parlementaires, le Journal des sessions de la chambre des Lords, les factures et les lois d’intérêt privé et local de 1700 à 1834. Vous trouverez des exemples à l’adresse suivante:<br><a class="link"   href="http://www.southampton.ac.uk/library/ldu/parl18c.html" >http://www.southampton.ac.uk/library/ldu/parl18c.html <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><strong>Numérisation des pamphlets datant du 19ème siècle:</strong> plus de 23 000 pamphlets datant du 19ème siècle provenant de bibliothèques de recherche couvrant le paysage économique et socio-politique de Grande-Bretagne ont été numérisés par la LDU et convertis au format PDF interrogeable. Les détails du projet et les entrées du catalogue sont disponibles à l’adresse suivante: <a class="link"   href="http://www.britishpamphlets.org.uk/" >http://www.britishpamphlets.org.uk/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>D’autres projets internes incluent:</p><p><strong>Numérisation des thèses de doctorat:</strong> les copies numérisées de 20 000 de ces thèses récompensées de l’université de Southampton ont été converties en PDF interrogeable et sont à présent disponibles via le référentiel de recherche institutionnelle de l’université, Eprints Soton. Eprints Soton dispose de copies électroniques des résultats de recherche, notamment d’articles de journaux, de chapitres de livres, de documents de conférence et de thèses. Des manuscrits et des documents papier non publiés sont également disponibles. L’intégralité du texte de nombreux de ces éléments est gratuitement disponible en fonction des autorisations liées au droit d’auteur et des autorisations accordées à l’utilisateur final. <a class="link"   href="http://eprints.soton.ac.uk/" >http://eprints.soton.ac.uk/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><strong>Numérisation des documents parlementaires relatifs à l’Irlande (EPPI):</strong> environ 15 000 documents parlementaires, de 1801 à 1922, ont été numérisés et mis à disposition sous la forme de fichiers PDF interrogeables via des liens du catalogue de l’université.</p><p><strong>Numérisation de textes de cours:</strong> la bibliothèque convertit les documents imprimés au format PDF interrogeable afin de soutenir les cours nécessitant une grande quantité de textes. Dans le cadre de la licence accordée par l’organisme de concession de licences de droits d’auteur (CLA, Copyright Licencing Agency) du Royaume-Uni, l’accès aux fichiers PDF interrogeables se limite aux utilisateurs de l’université via le catalogue de la bibliothèque.</p><p><strong>La collection Richard Rutt:</strong> une collection de livres de tricot datant du 19ème siècle provenant de la bibliothèque de références artistiques de l’école Winchester a été numérisée et mise à disposition sous la forme de fichiers PDF interrogeables via Internet.</p><h2 id="Conclusion"><a href="#Conclusion" class="headerlink" title="Conclusion"></a>Conclusion</h2><p>La reconnaissance optique de caractères puissante et précise est une partie intégrante des activités de l’unité de numérisation de bibliothèques. Grâce à l’augmentation de la production engendrée par ABBYY Recognition Server, le personnel de la bibliothèque est libéré du travail ennuyeux que constitue l’OCR manuel. Des millions de pages de documents provenant de la collection de l’université de Southampton sont disponibles en ligne dans des formats numériques pour les étudiants et pour le reste du monde.</p><p>La réussite de la numérisation peut également être attribuée à la souplesse d´administration du produit et à la facilité de son intégration aux processus de bibliothèques existants. « La possibilité d’intégrer ABBYY Recognition Server à notre workflow était capitale, » a déclaré Julian Ball, administrateur de section de l’unité de numérisation de bibliothèques.</p><p>« L’installation d’ABBYY Recognition Server a été rapide. Les premières réponses d’ABBYY et de leurs équipes de support vis-à-vis de toutes les questions posées ont été rapides, avec un suivi de bonne qualité. Nous avons été très satisfaits des résultats et nous avons hâte d’utiliser le produit pour continuer à remplir nos objectifs en termes de numérisation. »</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ephamedtechinc.pxf.io/c/5597632/2097466/26400?prodsku=B700" target="_top" id="2097466"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/26400-2097466"                      border="0" alt="" width="2048" height="1024"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2097466/26400"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="A-propos-de-l’universite-de-Southampton"><a href="#A-propos-de-l’universite-de-Southampton" class="headerlink" title="À propos de l’université de Southampton"></a>À propos de l’université de Southampton</h2><p>L’unité de numérisation de bibliothèques de l’université de Southampton propose<br>un service de numérisation aux bibliothèques, aux archives et au secteur commercial. Depuis 2003, nous nous sommes spécialisés dans la capture numérique d’images et de texte issus de documents, que ces documents soient reliés ou non, afin de les conserver.</p><p>Contact: <a class="link"   href="http://www.soton.ac.uk/library/ldu" >www.soton.ac.uk/library/ldu <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><hr><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ukaidot.sjv.io/c/5597632/1793237/19578" target="_top" id="1793237"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/19578-1793237"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="1200"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1793237/19578"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="A-propos-d’ABBYY-et-contact"><a href="#A-propos-d’ABBYY-et-contact" class="headerlink" title="À propos d’ABBYY et contact"></a>À propos d’ABBYY et contact</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Vers la description d’ABBYY › <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contacts › <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Partager </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.movavi.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=MOVAVI&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.movavi.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3DBanner%2B728x90"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://mcusercontent.com/0885a03ded3d480dca9287f12/images/2e76fe6a-3010-1b37-7846-f34ff9c6b4ca.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Pret-a-parler-a-un-expert"><a href="#Pret-a-parler-a-un-expert" class="headerlink" title="Prêt à parler à un expert ?"></a>Prêt à parler à un expert ?</h3><p>Nous serions ravis de vous aider tout au long de votre parcours d’automatisation.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contactez-nous <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Southampton-University-Digitizes-Massive-Print-Collections-Enhancing-Accessibility-for-Students-and-Researchers&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Southampt</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Revolutionizing Workflows with ABBYY: Discover the Next Generation RPA Solutions for Modern Enterprises</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/revolutionizing-workflows-with-abbyy-discover-the-next-generation-rpa-solutions-for-modern-enterprises/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/revolutionizing-workflows-with-abbyy-discover-the-next-generation-rpa-solutions-for-modern-enterprises/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.882Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.882Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Revolutionizing-Workflows-with-ABBYY-Discover-the-Next-Generation-RPA-Solutions-for-Modern-Enterprises"><a href="#Revolutionizing-Workflows-with-ABBYY-Discover-the-Next-Generation-RPA-Solutions-for-Modern-Enterprises" class="headerlink" title="Revolutionizing Workflows with ABBYY: Discover the Next Generation RPA Solutions for Modern Enterprises"></a>Revolutionizing Workflows with ABBYY: Discover the Next Generation RPA Solutions for Modern Enterprises</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="The-Modern-Age-“Machine-Gun”-for-Successful-and-Enterprise-wide-RPA"><a href="#The-Modern-Age-“Machine-Gun”-for-Successful-and-Enterprise-wide-RPA" class="headerlink" title="The Modern Age “Machine Gun” for Successful and Enterprise-wide RPA"></a>The Modern Age “Machine Gun” for Successful and Enterprise-wide RPA</h2><h6 id="Joe-Rayfield"><a href="#Joe-Rayfield" class="headerlink" title="Joe Rayfield"></a>Joe Rayfield</h6><p>October 01, 2019</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25380/11090_smm_blog_the-modern-age-machine-gun-for-successful-and-enterprise-wide-rpa_2blog.png"                      alt="the modern age &quot;machine gun&quot; for successful and enterprise-wide RPA | ABBYY Blog Post"                > </p><p>RPA or Robotic Process Automation is definitely a hot topic. The reason is obvious: process automation done correctly can dramatically reduce cost, while increasing both the speed and accuracy of process execution.</p><p>As demand and expectations skyrocket, RPA vendors and adopters alike are finding their initiatives unintentionally and often unnecessarily gated by two major factors:</p><ul><li>The time and effort required by the pre-RPA process discovery and benchmarking of the as-is state. How do we know what to automate next and why?</li><li>The post-RPA requirement to quantify savings, monitor performance, control compliance, and an ability to advertise success and further scale automation throughout the enterprise.</li></ul><p>Why are these two factors acting as the proverbial “ball and chain” of our automation efforts — because both are still typically run as highly manual efforts– and therefore are time consuming, costly, and open to error.</p><p>There simply is no reason for either of those activities to remain in the Medieval Times. Raising your Process IQ is critical for your organization across the board!</p><p><strong>BOLD STATEMENT ALERT</strong>: Before I go on — Don’t tell me you don’t have the data — it is there — go and find it, and if you really don’t have it — start creating it!! If you have serious ambitions of transforming your enterprise operations through RPA, Machine Learning and AI, utilizing Process Intelligence to understand your business process data will be absolutely critical in your organization’s success.</p><h2 id="How-does-a-Process-Intelligence-Platform-support-RPA"><a href="#How-does-a-Process-Intelligence-Platform-support-RPA" class="headerlink" title="How does a Process Intelligence Platform support RPA?"></a>How does a Process Intelligence Platform support RPA?</h2><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://coinrule.sjv.io/c/5597632/1958374/18409" target="_top" id="1958374"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18409-1958374"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="300"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1958374/18409"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Pre-RPA-Implementation"><a href="#Pre-RPA-Implementation" class="headerlink" title="Pre-RPA Implementation"></a>Pre-RPA Implementation</h3><p>Firstly, <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Intelligence <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> should be used during the pre-implementation analysis of existing processes to highlight the ideal candidates for an RPA both in terms of process efficiency goals and to define realistic Return on Investment expectations.</p><p>This increased Process IQ delivers 100% end to end process visibility through the creation of an interactive digital process twin, created in a fraction of the time of the historically manual process assessments. Once a process twin has been created — Process Intelligence will easily allow your organization to quickly identify the bottlenecks in business processes — so you can see the areas where manual steps are causing compliance and audit challenges, rework and repeated steps. These resource intensive, error-prone manual steps are prime candidates for <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >an RPA implementation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Essentially a Process Intelligence Platform should act as your RPA roadmap, identifying, prioritizing and justifying the right processes to attack — or as one of our customers calls it — “Evidence Based RPA Planning”</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.textstudio.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=35633281&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"> <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/d6eb8222c9718486bdabce8b897380f7/products/2_premium-icon.png"                      border="0"                > Take advantage of PREMIUM features.<br>Create your texts &#x2F; logos without any limitation.<br>No attribution required when downloading.<br>No advertising on the website.<br> TextStudio.com  PREMIUM - Monthly Membership</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Post-RPA-implementation"><a href="#Post-RPA-implementation" class="headerlink" title="Post RPA-implementation"></a>Post RPA-implementation</h3><p>We all need to remember that whilst the discovery and analysis components of a Process Intelligence deployment can provide great value in a process assessment, it is hardly the final destination! The ultimate goal is to improve them, whether this be achieved through staff training, process re-engineering or through automation. This is the area where a “True” Process Intelligence Platform can deliver unmatched functionality.</p><p>When you have chosen the right processes to automate using your desired RPA tool, Process Intelligence Platforms will continuously monitor the execution in near real time and immediately alert you when any of the violations or exceptions occur.</p><p>To be fair, some monitoring capabilities may already exist in BPM or RPA platforms; however, they will only work for the fragments of the business processes managed by those platforms and only for simple issues like time delay. A Process Intelligence Platform watches over the entire process, from start to finish, as it crosses multiple systems and identifies even the most complex issues based on multiple types of prebuilt analysis. Also, while general Business Intelligence tools can provide point in time metrics about the robot’s performance — this falls woefully short of truly understanding the change that the robots are having on the entire process. Process Intelligence can both monitor the performance of the Robots — but also the pre and post patterns that dictate overall compliance and effectiveness of the project. Throw in both pre and post implementation cost-based analytics — and a proven ROI can immediately be constructed, tracked and internally advertised.</p><p>A further piece of the puzzle and potentially one of the most important ones is that Process Intelligence Platforms can not only alert people of process deviations, but they can also trigger Process Management or Robotic Process Automation platforms to remedy the identified issues automatically. Just think about that — you may even achieve the Holy Grail of operational excellence — the closed loop integration where your process intelligence tool monitors your operational platforms, notifies it when a special condition occurs, triggers the remedy, then verifies the problem is actually solved. And if you throw in predictive capabilities for a future process state — creating an opportunity for interventional automation — now I am getting really excited (Someone cool me down)!!</p><p>If you still don’t yet have a blue print for intelligent automation or your operational transformation in 2019 you still have time to plan. If your organization is prioritizing digital transformation and truly wants to accelerate their success — a Process Intelligence Platform is an absolutely critical piece of the puzzle.</p><p>Don’t get left fighting with swords!</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/artificial-intelligence-ai/"  title="Artificial Intelligence (AI)">Artificial Intelligence (AI) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Enterprise <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Mining <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/robotic-process-automation-rpa/"  title="Robotic Process Automation (RPA)">Robotic Process Automation (RPA) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25707/josephrayfield-99x99.png"                      alt="Joseph Rayfield ABBYY"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.revouninstaller.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=27889512&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/4282ec8de8c9be897e7aff4aa231b1a4/728__90.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p>Joe Rayfield</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.nero.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=42296740&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.nero.com/nero-com-wAssets/img/banners/2023/biu/Nero_BackItUp_Screen_2.webp"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Revolutionizing-Workflows-with-ABBYY-Discover-the-Next-Generation-RPA-Solutions-for-Modern-Enterprises&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Revolutionizing-Wo</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Optimizing Procedures for Reduced Expenditure in Finance Management Services</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/optimizing-procedures-for-reduced-expenditure-in-finance-management-services/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/optimizing-procedures-for-reduced-expenditure-in-finance-management-services/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.870Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.870Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Optimizing-Procedures-for-Reduced-Expenditure-in-Finance-Management-Services"><a href="#Optimizing-Procedures-for-Reduced-Expenditure-in-Finance-Management-Services" class="headerlink" title="Optimizing Procedures for Reduced Expenditure in Finance Management Services"></a>Optimizing Procedures for Reduced Expenditure in Finance Management Services</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Webinars <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Transforming-Operations-to-Drive-Cost-Efficiency-in-Financial-Services"><a href="#Transforming-Operations-to-Drive-Cost-Efficiency-in-Financial-Services" class="headerlink" title="Transforming Operations to Drive Cost-Efficiency in Financial Services"></a>Transforming Operations to Drive Cost-Efficiency in Financial Services</h2><p>English</p><h3 id="Featuring"><a href="#Featuring" class="headerlink" title="Featuring"></a>Featuring</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/33590/87-stephenwalker-198x198.png"                      alt="Stephan Walker"                ></p><h3 id="Stephan-Walker"><a href="#Stephan-Walker" class="headerlink" title="Stephan Walker"></a>Stephan Walker</h3><p>Lead Analyst, Financial Services, <strong>GlobalData Financial Services</strong></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25122/logo-2021-76x23.svg"                      alt="Cheryl Chiodi"                > </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ephamedtechinc.pxf.io/c/5597632/2097466/26400?prodsku=B700" target="_top" id="2097466"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/26400-2097466"                      border="0" alt="" width="2048" height="1024"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2097466/26400"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/32900/75-cherylchiodi-198x198.png"                      alt="Cheryl Chiodi"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.nero.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=42296855&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="http://cdnwww.nero.com/nero-com-wAssets/img/banners/2023/recode/Nero_Recode_Screen_2.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://aspironcom.sjv.io/c/5597632/1941789/21554" target="_top" id="1941789"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/21554-1941789"                      border="0" alt="" width="650" height="800"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1941789/21554"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Cheryl-Chiodi"><a href="#Cheryl-Chiodi" class="headerlink" title="Cheryl Chiodi"></a>Cheryl Chiodi</h3><p>Director of Solution Marketing, <strong>ABBYY</strong></p><h3 id="Overview"><a href="#Overview" class="headerlink" title="Overview"></a>Overview</h3><p>Financial institutions are looking for ways to reduce costs while maintaining their competitive advantage. Increasing competition, low interest rates and the corrosive effects of the global pandemic have culminated into a vicelike squeeze on already shrinking margins. To survive, banks must focus on taking a strategic approach to cost efficiency and effectiveness.</p><p>If your organization is like most, and you’re looking to quickly operationalize this strategic approach, intelligent process automation can help.</p><h3 id="Improve-operational-excellence"><a href="#Improve-operational-excellence" class="headerlink" title="Improve operational excellence"></a>Improve operational excellence</h3><p>Find out how financial institutions can reduce friction and simplify processes to serve customers in an easy and intuitive way with intelligent automation.</p><p>Watch this webinar to:</p><ul><li>Discover the importance of personalized customer experiences in a virtual environment</li><li>Explore how digital workers can free up knowledge workers for value-add activities</li><li>Understand the power of mobile to amplify brand presence, deepen customer relationships, and increase revenue</li></ul><h3 id="Watch-now"><a href="#Watch-now" class="headerlink" title="Watch now"></a>Watch now</h3><h3 id="Get-in-touch-with-us"><a href="#Get-in-touch-with-us" class="headerlink" title="Get in touch with us"></a>Get in touch with us</h3><p>Please note that progressive profiling is used on this form to incrementally collect profile data over time.<br>All personal information collected via this method is under full scope of all provisions in our privacy policy.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://caperobbin.sjv.io/c/5597632/2006118/18460" target="_top" id="2006118"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18460-2006118"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2006118/18460"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Thank-you-enjoy-your-webinar"><a href="#Thank-you-enjoy-your-webinar" class="headerlink" title="Thank you, enjoy your webinar!"></a>Thank you, enjoy your webinar!</h2><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SUlJCCJcGHg"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/33597/transforming-operations.jpg"                      alt="Transforming Operations"                ></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.nero.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=42296985&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/9cea886b9f44a3c2df1163730ab64994/products/copy_nero_burning_rom_cart.png"                      border="0"                ><br></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=37100474&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://awario.com/images/pages/index/img-leads-1280@1x.avif"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY"><a href="#Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Have questions? Contact ABBYY"></a>Have questions? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar"><a href="#Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar" class="headerlink" title="Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:"></a>Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:</h4><p>First name*</p><p>Last name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Phone</p><p>Company*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Query string</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Optimizing-Procedures-for-Reduced-Expenditure-in-Finance-Management-Services&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Optimizing-Procedures-for-Reduced-Expenditur</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Optimized with Advanced Web Tracking Technology: Powered by the Leading Analytics Platform, Cookiebot</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/optimized-with-advanced-web-tracking-technology-powered-by-the-leading-analytics-platform-cookiebot/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/optimized-with-advanced-web-tracking-technology-powered-by-the-leading-analytics-platform-cookiebot/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.862Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.862Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Optimized-with-Advanced-Web-Tracking-Technology-Powered-by-the-Leading-Analytics-Platform-Cookiebot"><a href="#Optimized-with-Advanced-Web-Tracking-Technology-Powered-by-the-Leading-Analytics-Platform-Cookiebot" class="headerlink" title="Optimized with Advanced Web Tracking Technology: Powered by the Leading Analytics Platform, Cookiebot"></a>Optimized with Advanced Web Tracking Technology: Powered by the Leading Analytics Platform, Cookiebot</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="tangro®-Elevates-Document-Processing-Availability-Thanks-to-ABBYY"><a href="#tangro®-Elevates-Document-Processing-Availability-Thanks-to-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="tangro® Elevates Document Processing Availability Thanks to ABBYY"></a>tangro® Elevates Document Processing Availability Thanks to ABBYY</h2><p>June 30, 2016</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><p><em><strong>New functionality in integrated OCR technology strengthens fail-safe processing capabilities of SAP-based document management solution</strong></em> </p><p>ABBYY, a leading provider of document recognition, data capture, and linguistic technologies, announced that <a class="link"   href="http://www.tangro.de/en.html" >tangro software components GmbH. <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> has further increased the reliability of its document processing solutions through integration of a new component of the ABBYY OCR technology. The Germany-based provider of embedded SAP solutions and long-standing ABBYY customer integrates ABBYY’s optical character recognition (OCR) technology for document digitisation and text recognition in its software for automated document processing. tangro uses text recognition to provide the foundation for extraction of data and their later processing in SAP. A new feature in the ABBYY OCR toolkit, the redundant network licence manager, ensures continuous and fail-safe text recognition of all incoming documents in tangro’s applications. As a result, users of tangro software benefit from the overall increased availability of the document processing system.  </p><p>tangro is an expert in the automated processing of incoming documents in SAP. The tangro Inbound Suite is a comprehensive solution, embedded in the SAP environment, with the ability to process thousands of documents every day. For several years now, tangro has been using the Software Development Kit ABBYY FineReader Engine. The integrated OCR technology converts text in scanned documents into editable and structured data, which is automatically passed on to the corresponding SAP workflows. Any failure of the system would strongly impair all subsequent processes, generate costs for system recovery and increase the risk of data loss – especially when processing extensive document volumes.  </p><p>To ensure a steady and reliable OCR process, multiple processing stations can be deployed within the network. The redundant network licence manager, now offered as part of the ABBYY OCR SDK, helps to increase the system’s availability. To ensure continuous OCR processing, the network licence manager component can be installed on different hardware systems in a cluster architecture. This way, the document processing operation runs reliably and text recognition is still performed by the various workstations even in the unlikely event of the licence server failure.</p><p><em>“Licence server failures might be rare, but they are fatal – if the text recognition process is interrupted, the entire document processing solution stops working. The redundant network licence manager allows us to offer our clients maximum availability and highest process reliability,”</em> explains Dominik Pfizenmaier, software developer at tangro software components GmbH. <em>“ABBYY’s technical support team provided great support during the implementation phase. We are using the new function already in various projects and it works ultra-reliably. Thanks to ABBYY, we can guarantee the necessary operational reliability to our clients and further strengthen our position on the market.”</em> </p><p>With its broad set of tools, ABBYY offers developers the ability to integrate high accuracy optical text recognition into their applications. ABBYY recognition technology transforms images of text into searchable and editable formats for checking against a database. With accurate ABBYY OCR technology, developers can extend the functionality of a wide variety of applications on different platforms including Windows, Mac OS, Linux, mobile platforms for iOS and Android, as well as OCR service in the Cloud that can be reached via API. See more at: <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" > <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/ocr-sdk/" >https://www.abbyy.com/ocr-sdk/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>  </p><p><strong>About ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY is a leading global provider of technologies and solutions that help businesses to action information. The company sets the standard in content capture and innovative language-based technologies that integrate across the information lifecycle. ABBYY solutions are relied on to optimise business processes, mitigate risk, accelerate decision making and drive revenue. ABBYY technologies are used and licensed by some of the largest international enterprises and government organisations, as well as small and medium businesses and individuals. ABBYY UK Ltd. is a member of the ABBYY Group supporting sales and marketing activities in Western Europe. The ABBYY Group maintains offices in Germany, the UK, France, Spain, Ukraine, Cyprus, the United States, Canada, Australia, UAE, Japan and Taiwan. For more information, visit <a class="link"   href="http://www.abbyy.com/" >www.ABBYY.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><em>ABBYY, the ABBYY Logo</em> <em>and FineReader</em> <em>are either registered trademarks or trademarks of ABBYY Software Ltd. SAP is the trademark or registered trademark of SAP SE in Germany and in several other countries. Other product names mentioned herein may be trademarks and&#x2F;or registered trademarks of their respective owners and are hereby recognised.</em> </p><p><strong>About tangro software components gmbh</strong></p><p><a class="link"   href="http://www.tangro.de/" >tangro software components gmbh <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> is the SAP specialist for inbound document management, with over 30 years of experience with SAP. tangro supports companies in optimising and automating their inbound document business processes for all incoming channels (paper, fax, e-mail EDI, etc.). tangro’s patented application architecture allows it to develop software in a particularly effective manner and to quickly and cost-effectively meet individual requirements.</p><p><strong>Additional information:</strong></p><p>ABBYY Europe GmbH<br>Agata Zesch-Fronc<br>Elsenheimerstraße 49<br>80687 Munich, Germany<br>Tel.: +49 89 69 33 33 0<br>Fax: +49 89 69 33 33 300<br>E-mail: press_<a class="link"   href="mailto:&#101;&#x75;&#64;&#x61;&#x62;&#x62;&#121;&#x79;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;" >&#101;&#x75;&#64;&#x61;&#x62;&#x62;&#121;&#x79;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#x6d; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br>Web: <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=3727260&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="http://www.aiseesoft.com/avangate/30p/banner.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Optimized-with-Advanced-Web-Tracking-Technology-Powered-by-the-Leading-Analytics-Platform-Cookiebot&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Optimized-with-Advanc</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Navigating New Norms in Banking with Artificial Intelligence &amp; Digital Advancements Post-Corona – Expertise From a Leading ABBYY Analyst</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/navigating-new-norms-in-banking-with-artificial-intelligence-and-digital-advancements-post-corona-expertise-from-a-leading-abbyy-analyst/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/navigating-new-norms-in-banking-with-artificial-intelligence-and-digital-advancements-post-corona-expertise-from-a-leading-abbyy-analyst/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.855Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.855Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Navigating-New-Norms-in-Banking-with-Artificial-Intelligence-Digital-Advancements-Post-Corona-–-Expertise-From-a-Leading-ABBYY-Analyst"><a href="#Navigating-New-Norms-in-Banking-with-Artificial-Intelligence-Digital-Advancements-Post-Corona-–-Expertise-From-a-Leading-ABBYY-Analyst" class="headerlink" title="Navigating New Norms in Banking with Artificial Intelligence &amp; Digital Advancements Post-Corona – Expertise From a Leading ABBYY Analyst"></a>Navigating New Norms in Banking with Artificial Intelligence &amp; Digital Advancements Post-Corona – Expertise From a Leading ABBYY Analyst</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Webinars <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Kunstliche-Intelligenz-und-Digitalisierung-im-Post-Corona-Banking"><a href="#Kunstliche-Intelligenz-und-Digitalisierung-im-Post-Corona-Banking" class="headerlink" title="Künstliche Intelligenz und Digitalisierung im Post-Corona-Banking"></a>Künstliche Intelligenz und Digitalisierung im Post-Corona-Banking</h2><p>German</p><h3 id="Sprecher"><a href="#Sprecher" class="headerlink" title="Sprecher"></a>Sprecher</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25132/retarus-logo-forspeakers.png"                      alt="09 Ebernardrohe 198X198"                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25116/09-ebernardrohe-198x198.png"                      alt="09 Ebernardrohe 198X198"                ></p><h3 id="Eberhard-Rohe"><a href="#Eberhard-Rohe" class="headerlink" title="Eberhard Rohe"></a>Eberhard Rohe</h3><p>Account Director, <strong>Retarus</strong></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35547/kfw-logo-forspeakers-86x44.jpg"                      alt="37 Oliverbohl 198X198"                > </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://bluettieu.pxf.io/c/5597632/2042323/17091" target="_top" id="2042323"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17091-2042323"                      border="0" alt="BLUETTI NEW LAUNCH AC180T" width="3840" height="1600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2042323/17091"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/28979/37-oliverbohl-198x198.png"                      alt="37 Oliverbohl 198X198"                ></p><h3 id="Dr-Oliver-Bohl"><a href="#Dr-Oliver-Bohl" class="headerlink" title="Dr. Oliver Bohl"></a>Dr. Oliver Bohl</h3><p>Director Digital Channels, <strong>KfW Bankengruppe</strong></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/29273/dz-privatbank-forspeakers.png"                      alt="39 Matthiasabel 198X198"                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/29271/39-matthiasabel-198x198.png"                      alt="39 Matthiasabel 198X198"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://aidotcom.pxf.io/c/5597632/2086436/19576" target="_top" id="2086436"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/19576-2086436"                      border="0" alt="" width="1500" height="400"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2086436/19576"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Matthias-Abel"><a href="#Matthias-Abel" class="headerlink" title="Matthias Abel"></a>Matthias Abel</h3><p>Gruppenleiter Insti- und Direktkundenservice, <strong>DZ Direktbank</strong></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35123/logo-2021-90x27.svg"                      alt="02 Alexandrejanicki 198X198"                > </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.nero.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=42570605&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="http://cdnwww.nero.com/nero-com-wAssets/img/banners/2023/usbXcopy/Nero_USB_x_copy_Screen_2.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25101/02-alexandrejanicki-198x198.png"                      alt="02 Alexandrejanicki 198X198"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2082532/7443" target="_top" id="2082532"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2082532"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2082532/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://zonlipartnershipprogram.pxf.io/c/5597632/1596691/17882" target="_top" id="1596691"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17882-1596691"                      border="0" alt="" width="728" height="90"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1596691/17882"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Alexandre-Janicki"><a href="#Alexandre-Janicki" class="headerlink" title="Alexandre Janicki"></a>Alexandre Janicki</h3><p>Senior Enterprise Sales Manager, <strong>ABBYY</strong></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25121/logo-2021-90x27.svg"                      alt="38 Marlenewolfgruber 198X198"                > </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://turtlebeachus.sjv.io/c/5597632/1988416/23719" target="_top" id="1988416"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/23719-1988416"                      border="0" alt="" width="600" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1988416/23719"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/28977/38-marlenewolfgruber-198x198.png"                      alt="38 Marlenewolfgruber 198X198"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.incomedia.eu/order/checkout.php?PRODS=12730965&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://incomedia.eu/files/images/affiliates/w5/03_WBSX5_728x90_red_CTA.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Dr-Marlene-Wolfgruber"><a href="#Dr-Marlene-Wolfgruber" class="headerlink" title="Dr. Marlene Wolfgruber"></a>Dr. Marlene Wolfgruber</h3><p>Director of Product Marketing Mobile, <strong>ABBYY</strong></p><h3 id="Ubersicht"><a href="#Ubersicht" class="headerlink" title="Übersicht"></a>Übersicht</h3><p>In diesem Webinar dreht sich alles um die großen Handlungsfelder von Banken im „Post-Corona-Zeitalter“. Dr. Oliver Bohl, Direktor Digitale Kanäle bei der KfW Bankengruppe, spricht als direkt Betroffener über die Auswirkungen von COVID-19 auf Arbeitsprozesse und Kundenkommunikation im Bankensektor. Welche Chancen Ihnen der Einsatz von künstlicher Intelligenz, digitalisierten Prozessen und Cloudifizierung ermöglicht, das zeigen in diesem Webinar Matthias Abel von der DZ PRIVATBANK, Eberhard Rohe, Account Director bei Retarus, sowie Alexandre Janicki und Dr. Marlene Wolfgruber von ABBYY anhand von Praxisbeispielen.</p><h3 id="Das-sind-die-Themen"><a href="#Das-sind-die-Themen" class="headerlink" title="Das sind die Themen:"></a>Das sind die Themen:</h3><ul><li>First-hand Lehren aus der Corona-Krise</li><li>Mit künstlicher Intelligenz, Prozess-Digitalisierung und Cloudifizierung einen Schritt voraus sein</li><li>Automatisierung des Order-Prozesses am Beispiel der DZ-PRIVATBANK</li><li>Kunden-Onboarding und Identitätsprüfung einfach, schnell und rechtlich einwandfrei</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.copernic.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=41033091&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.2checkout.com/images/merchant/8d30aa96e72440759f74bd2306c1fa3d/Copernic-2023-Affiliate-728x90-Advanced.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Webinar-Aufzeichnung-hier-anfordern"><a href="#Webinar-Aufzeichnung-hier-anfordern" class="headerlink" title="Webinar-Aufzeichnung hier anfordern"></a>Webinar-Aufzeichnung hier anfordern</h3><h3 id="Get-in-touch-with-us"><a href="#Get-in-touch-with-us" class="headerlink" title="Get in touch with us"></a>Get in touch with us</h3><p>Please note that progressive profiling is used on this form to incrementally collect profile data over time.<br>All personal information collected via this method is under full scope of all provisions in our privacy policy.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4709458&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://3d-kstudio.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/Project-Manager-version-3-1600x900-768x419.jpg"                      border="0"                >Project Manager - Asset Browser for 3Ds Max</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Vielen-Dank-Wir-wunschen-Ihnen-viel-Spas-mit-dem-Webinar"><a href="#Vielen-Dank-Wir-wunschen-Ihnen-viel-Spas-mit-dem-Webinar" class="headerlink" title="Vielen Dank! Wir wünschen Ihnen viel Spaß mit dem Webinar."></a>Vielen Dank! Wir wünschen Ihnen viel Spaß mit dem Webinar.</h2><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vjY4sTE9GJ0"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/29413/12-ki-und-digitalisierung-im-post-corona-banking.jpg"                      alt="12 KI Und Digitalisierung Im Post Corona Banking"                ></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://propmoneyinc.pxf.io/c/5597632/1803115/14559" target="_top" id="1803115"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/14559-1803115"                      border="0" alt="" width="859" height="859"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1803115/14559"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY"><a href="#Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Have questions? Contact ABBYY"></a>Have questions? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar"><a href="#Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar" class="headerlink" title="Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:"></a>Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:</h4><p>First name*</p><p>Last name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Phone</p><p>Company*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Query string</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Navigating-New-Norms-in-Banking-with-Artificial-Intelligence-Digital-Advancements-Post-Corona-–-Expertise-From-a-Leading-ABBYY-Analy</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Master the Art of On-Page SEO: Effective Strategies to Elevate Your Website&#39;s Visibility in Google Searches</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/master-the-art-of-on-page-seo-effective-strategies-to-elevate-your-websites-visibility-in-google-searches/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/master-the-art-of-on-page-seo-effective-strategies-to-elevate-your-websites-visibility-in-google-searches/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.844Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.844Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Master-the-Art-of-On-Page-SEO-Effective-Strategies-to-Elevate-Your-Website’s-Visibility-in-Google-Searches"><a href="#Master-the-Art-of-On-Page-SEO-Effective-Strategies-to-Elevate-Your-Website’s-Visibility-in-Google-Searches" class="headerlink" title="Master the Art of On-Page SEO: Effective Strategies to Elevate Your Website’s Visibility in Google Searches"></a>Master the Art of On-Page SEO: Effective Strategies to Elevate Your Website’s Visibility in Google Searches</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Retourner aux expériences clients <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Information &amp; Communication | Document Classification</p><h2 id="Les-solutions-M-Files-integrent-la-technologie-d’intelligence-artificielle-d’ABBYY-pour-automatiser-la-gestion-de-l’information"><a href="#Les-solutions-M-Files-integrent-la-technologie-d’intelligence-artificielle-d’ABBYY-pour-automatiser-la-gestion-de-l’information" class="headerlink" title="Les solutions M-Files intègrent la technologie d’intelligence artificielle d’ABBYY pour automatiser la gestion de l’information"></a>Les solutions M-Files intègrent la technologie d’intelligence artificielle d’ABBYY pour automatiser la gestion de l’information</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/fr/66417.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Retourner aux expériences clients <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Les-solutions-M-Files-integrent-la-technologie-d’intelligence-artificielle-d’ABBYY-pour-automatiser-la-gestion-de-l’information-1"><a href="#Les-solutions-M-Files-integrent-la-technologie-d’intelligence-artificielle-d’ABBYY-pour-automatiser-la-gestion-de-l’information-1" class="headerlink" title="Les solutions M-Files intègrent la technologie d’intelligence artificielle d’ABBYY pour automatiser la gestion de l’information"></a>Les solutions M-Files intègrent la technologie d’intelligence artificielle d’ABBYY pour automatiser la gestion de l’information</h2><p>Télécom et TIC | Classification de documents </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://propmoneyinc.pxf.io/c/5597632/1803115/14559" target="_top" id="1803115"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/14559-1803115"                      border="0" alt="" width="859" height="859"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1803115/14559"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Pret-a-parler-a-un-expert"><a href="#Pret-a-parler-a-un-expert" class="headerlink" title="Prêt à parler à un expert ?"></a>Prêt à parler à un expert ?</h3><p>Nous serions ravis de vous aider tout au long de votre parcours d’automatisation.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contactez-nous <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Master-the-Art-of-On-Page-SEO-Effective-Strategies-to-Elevate-Your-Website’s-Visibility-in-Google-Searches&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Master-the-Art</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Marlin Equity Partners Secures New Equity Position in Leading OCR Firm, ABBYY</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/marlin-equity-partners-secures-new-equity-position-in-leading-ocr-firm-abbyy/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/marlin-equity-partners-secures-new-equity-position-in-leading-ocr-firm-abbyy/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.841Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.841Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Marlin-Equity-Partners-Secures-New-Equity-Position-in-Leading-OCR-Firm-ABBYY"><a href="#Marlin-Equity-Partners-Secures-New-Equity-Position-in-Leading-OCR-Firm-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Marlin Equity Partners Secures New Equity Position in Leading OCR Firm, ABBYY"></a>Marlin Equity Partners Secures New Equity Position in Leading OCR Firm, ABBYY</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="What-the-New-Investment-From-Marlin-Equity-Partners-Means-to-ABBYY"><a href="#What-the-New-Investment-From-Marlin-Equity-Partners-Means-to-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="What the New Investment From Marlin Equity Partners Means to ABBYY"></a>What the New Investment From Marlin Equity Partners Means to ABBYY</h2><p>May 27, 2021</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/33048/marlin-blog-cover-1.jpg"                                     > </p><p>On May 11th, we announced a significant investment by global technology-focused investment firm <a class="link"   href="https://www.marlinequity.com/" >Marlin Equity Partners <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, making it the largest shareholder of ABBYY. We are excited about this investment for several reasons. Mainly, it will accelerate growth for the company and provide the necessary capital to continue ABBYY’s history of highly respected and global innovations—our Digital Intelligence product portfolio.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >What is Digital Intelligence, and why do you need it to succeed at digital transformation? Learn more here! <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>More than 5,000 customers use our solutions in diverse industries, including finance, healthcare, supply chain, insurance, and more. We are proud to have ABBYY solutions currently used by global companies like PwC, FDA, Siemens, Deutsche Post DHL, PepsiCo, and Volkswagen.</p><p>Our entire <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Digital Intelligence platform <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> enables enterprises to effectively execute transformation strategies through the speedy and accurate capture of data at scale with a contextual understanding of scanned documents through ABBYY’s Intelligent Document Processing (IDP), Process Intelligence, and natural language processing capabilities. You’ll see more innovative solutions coming to market faster that will help enterprises reimagine how they get work done.</p><p>Additionally, we’ll continue to invest in exceeding our customers’ expectations. Our customers are our biggest advocates and working alongside them during every step of their digital transformation journey is core to our #OneABBYY values. From <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY University <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, to <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >online resources <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >webinars <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, our <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >partner ecosystems <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, or through our <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Professional Services <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> team, we are committed to ensuring Centers of Excellence, citizen developers, and IT get maximum value from their intelligent automation initiatives.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/32435/b-13.jpg"                      alt="two people wearing glasses smiling"                ></p><p>And, where would we be without our people? We plan on continuing to invest in our current workforce with the tools and skills they need to thrive. This also includes <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >attracting the best talent <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> globally, from developers to finance, to sales and marketing. It also means providing an engaging and diverse culture that empowers employees to feel impactful at work while also balancing home and social needs.</p><p>We hope our partners and customers see why we are excited about this investment. Marlin sees tremendous value in the success we’ve had and will be a strong, growth-oriented partner for our next phase of growth.</p><hr><p><strong>More Information</strong></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >https://www.abbyy.com/company/news/abbyy-completes-investment-from-marlin-equity-partners-to-accelerate-growth/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.marlinequity.com/marlin-completes-growth-equity-investment-in-abbyy/" >https://www.marlinequity.com/marlin-completes-growth-equity-investment-in-abbyy/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h5 id="Find-out-how-ABBYY-Digital-Intelligence-solutions-can-address-your-needs"><a href="#Find-out-how-ABBYY-Digital-Intelligence-solutions-can-address-your-needs" class="headerlink" title="Find out how ABBYY Digital Intelligence solutions can address your needs."></a><strong>Find out how ABBYY Digital Intelligence solutions can address your needs.</strong></h5><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Learn more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Enterprise <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ship7com.pxf.io/c/5597632/1509856/17634" target="_top" id="1509856"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17634-1509856"                      border="0" alt="" width="730" height="383"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Marlin-Equity-Partners-Secures-New-Equity-Position-in-Leading-OCR-Firm-ABBYY&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Marlin-Equity-Partners-Secures-New-Equity-Po</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Leveraging Cookiebot Technology for Advanced Site Engagement and SEO Success</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/leveraging-cookiebot-technology-for-advanced-site-engagement-and-seo-success/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/leveraging-cookiebot-technology-for-advanced-site-engagement-and-seo-success/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.833Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.833Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Leveraging-Cookiebot-Technology-for-Advanced-Site-Engagement-and-SEO-Success"><a href="#Leveraging-Cookiebot-Technology-for-Advanced-Site-Engagement-and-SEO-Success" class="headerlink" title="Leveraging Cookiebot Technology for Advanced Site Engagement and SEO Success"></a>Leveraging Cookiebot Technology for Advanced Site Engagement and SEO Success</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-Reduces-Customs-Document-Clearance-Time-by-more-than-90-to-Deliver-Commercial-Goods-to-Consumers-Faster"><a href="#ABBYY-Reduces-Customs-Document-Clearance-Time-by-more-than-90-to-Deliver-Commercial-Goods-to-Consumers-Faster" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Reduces Customs Document Clearance Time by more than 90% to Deliver Commercial Goods to Consumers Faster"></a>ABBYY Reduces Customs Document Clearance Time by more than 90% to Deliver Commercial Goods to Consumers Faster</h2><p>December 06, 2023</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/33811/news-colleagues8.jpg"                      alt="News Colleagues8"                > </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>’s intelligent document processing (IDP) solutions are helping manufacturers of fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) fast-track their trucks through border customs by reducing the time to clear custom clearances by more than 90%.</p><p>Trucks moving goods across international borders can be stalled for hours if there are any errors or discrepancies in their customs paperwork, resulting not only in delayed deliveries but also in potential fines or spoilage of goods.</p><p>Ireland-based pastry supplier <a class="link"   href="https://portumnapastry.com/" >Portumna Pastry Ltd <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> recently used ABBYY’s purpose-built AI to reduce their customs clearance times at the EU&#x2F;UK border from one hour to just five minutes. ABBYY IDP accelerated the customs clearance process by extracting data from complex transportation and logistics documents with 100% accuracy, allowing critical data to be submitted to national customs systems without the need for any manual review.</p><p>“From delivering frozen unbaked pastries to supermarkets to enabling global logistics carriers to deliver millions of manufacturing goods on time during peak seasons, time is of essence. Manufacturers and FMCGs no longer need to rely on brokerage firms to get their goods across international borders and into consumers’ households. They can take control over their customs operations by working with ABBYY and strategic solution partners to put their information to work.”</p><p><em>Neil Murphy, Chief Sales Officer at ABBYY</em></p><p>ABBYY engages directly with global carriers, freight forwarders, logistics providers and supply chain management providers and partners with strategic solution vendors who have simplified the complex processes of import and export.</p><p>“As a result of BREXIT, UK and EU businesses have had to face a massive increase in administration and paperwork when moving goods cross-border. Because a customs declaration is a legal document, there is no margin for error; an automated solution must be foolproof. With ABBYY IDP, we experience 100% accuracy and a 99% straight-through-processing rate.”</p><p><em>Joe Corcoran, Lead Consultant at CustomsTrack</em></p><p>ABBYY intelligent automation solutions are developed using the most advanced large language models specifically designed for purpose-built AI applications such as intelligent document processing. For more information about ABBYY solutions, visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/solutions/transportation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><h3 id="About-ABBYY"><a href="#About-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="About ABBYY"></a>About ABBYY</h3><p>ABBYY puts your information to work. We combine innovation and experience to transform data from business-critical documents into intelligent actionable outcomes in over 200 languages in real time. We enable more than 10,000 companies globally, including many of the Fortune 500, to drive significant impact where it matters most: customer experience, operational excellence, and competitive advantage. ABBYY is a global company with headquarters in Milpitas, CA and offices in 14 countries, and is the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Official Intelligent Automation Partner of Arsenal Women Football Club <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. For more information, visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/company/about-us/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and follow us on <a class="link"   href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/abbyy" >LinkedIn <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://twitter.com/ABBYY%5FSoftware" >Twitter <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://www.facebook.com/ABBYYsoft" >Facebook <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>ABBYY can either be a registered trademark or a trademark and can also be a logo, a company name (or part of it), or part of a product name of ABBYY group companies and may not be used without consent of its respective owners.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2082532/7443" target="_top" id="2082532"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2082532"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2082532/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="ABBYY-Editorial-Contact"><a href="#ABBYY-Editorial-Contact" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Editorial Contact"></a>ABBYY Editorial Contact</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/23662/02d-ginaray.png"                      alt="02D Ginaray"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://turtlebeachus.sjv.io/c/5597632/1988416/23719" target="_top" id="1988416"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/23719-1988416"                      border="0" alt="" width="600" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1988416/23719"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Gina-Ray"><a href="#Gina-Ray" class="headerlink" title="Gina Ray"></a>Gina Ray</h4><p><em>ABBYY</em></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >gina.ray@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Leveraging-Cookiebot-Technology-for-Advanced-Site-Engagement-and-SEO-Success&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Leveraging-Cookiebot-Technology-for-Advanced</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>IDP Implementation Strategies: Transforming the Future of Insurance Operations</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/idp-implementation-strategies-transforming-the-future-of-insurance-operations/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/idp-implementation-strategies-transforming-the-future-of-insurance-operations/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.827Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.827Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="IDP-Implementation-Strategies-Transforming-the-Future-of-Insurance-Operations"><a href="#IDP-Implementation-Strategies-Transforming-the-Future-of-Insurance-Operations" class="headerlink" title="IDP Implementation Strategies: Transforming the Future of Insurance Operations"></a>IDP Implementation Strategies: Transforming the Future of Insurance Operations</h2><p>eBook</p><h2 id="Intelligent-Document-Processing-in-Insurance-Use-Cases"><a href="#Intelligent-Document-Processing-in-Insurance-Use-Cases" class="headerlink" title="Intelligent Document Processing in Insurance: Use Cases"></a>Intelligent Document Processing in Insurance: Use Cases</h2><h3 id="Discover-the-best-use-cases-for-IDP-in-insurance"><a href="#Discover-the-best-use-cases-for-IDP-in-insurance" class="headerlink" title="Discover the best use cases for IDP in insurance"></a>Discover the best use cases for IDP in insurance</h3><p>Excel at customer satisfaction. Comply with regulations. Increase process efficiency. Insurers today have tall orders. They can no longer afford the delays and errors associated with legacy approaches to document processing. Purpose-built AI is now a must-have tool to drive process efficiency.</p><p>The data inside of insurance claims, correspondence, other documents contain a wealth of information to drive insurance processes—but only when that data is easily accessible, accurate, and able to inform action.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2075471/7443" target="_top" id="2075471"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2075471"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2075471/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Download-it-now"><a href="#Download-it-now" class="headerlink" title="Download it now!"></a>Download it now!</h3><p>This eBook shares eight impactful use cases where AI-driven intelligent document processing (IDP) is enabling our customers to achieve results like 80% reduction in manual data entry, 25% productivity increase in policy lifecycle, and 40% of incoming invoices processed automatically, including:</p><ul><li>Underwriting</li><li>Policy services</li><li>Claims management</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.systoolsgroup.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=SYSTOOBY&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.systoolsgroup.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3DSysTools%2BSQL%2BRecovery"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.systoolsgroup.com/box/sql-recovery.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Thank-you-for-your-interest-in-ABBYY"><a href="#Thank-you-for-your-interest-in-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Thank you for your interest in ABBYY."></a>Thank you for your interest in ABBYY.</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://abbyy.com/-/jssmedia/project/abbyy/abbyy/insights/resource-center/pdfs/ebook-use-case-insurance-intelligent-document-processing-en.pdf"  title="Read eBook">Read eBook <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form"><a href="#Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form" class="headerlink" title="Get your copy by filling in the form."></a>Get your copy by filling in the form.</h4><p>First name*</p><p>Last name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Salutation</p><p>Academic Title</p><p>Query string</p><p>Add your question or describe your interest</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>City</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;IDP-Implementation-Strategies-Transforming-the-Future-of-Insurance-Operations&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#IDP-Implementation-Strategies-Transforming-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How ABBYY Achieved a Remarkable 25%% Increase in Revenue for the Year 2N 2017</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/how-abbyy-achieved-a-remarkable-25-increase-in-revenue-for-the-year-2n-2017/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/how-abbyy-achieved-a-remarkable-25-increase-in-revenue-for-the-year-2n-2017/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.821Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.821Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="How-ABBYY-Achieved-a-Remarkable-25-Increase-in-Revenue-for-the-Year-2N-2017"><a href="#How-ABBYY-Achieved-a-Remarkable-25-Increase-in-Revenue-for-the-Year-2N-2017" class="headerlink" title="How ABBYY Achieved a Remarkable 25% Increase in Revenue for the Year 2N 2017"></a>How ABBYY Achieved a Remarkable 25% Increase in Revenue for the Year 2N 2017</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Actualités <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-annonce-une-augmentation-de-25-de-son-chiffre-d’affaires-en-2017"><a href="#ABBYY-annonce-une-augmentation-de-25-de-son-chiffre-d’affaires-en-2017" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY annonce une augmentation de 25 % de son chiffre d’affaires en 2017"></a>ABBYY annonce une augmentation de 25 % de son chiffre d’affaires en 2017</h2><p>14 février 2018</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><h4 id="La-multiplication-des-initiatives-de-transformation-numerique-d’intelligence-artificielle-et-d’automatisation-des-processus-par-la-robotique-favorise-la-croissance"><a href="#La-multiplication-des-initiatives-de-transformation-numerique-d’intelligence-artificielle-et-d’automatisation-des-processus-par-la-robotique-favorise-la-croissance" class="headerlink" title="La multiplication des initiatives de transformation numérique, d’intelligence artificielle et d’automatisation des processus par la robotique favorise la croissance"></a><em>La multiplication des initiatives de transformation numérique, d’intelligence artificielle et d’automatisation des processus par la robotique favorise la croissance</em></h4><p>ABBYY®, fournisseur mondial de solutions de capture de données intelligentes, annonce aujourd’hui ses résultats pour 2017. L’entreprise a enregistré une croissance de 25 % de son chiffre d’affaires, soit la plus forte progression en cinq ans.</p><p>En 2017, ABBYY a développé plusieurs projets de grande ampleur pour sa clientèle d’entreprises basée notamment aux Etats-Unis, en Europe ou en Australie. L’octroi de licences de technologie à des partenaires tels que Fujitsu, Epson, Hewlett Packard Enterprise, RICOH et Xerox est également une source de revenus significative pour l’entreprise.</p><p>La croissance d’ABBYY va de pair avec le développement des marchés liés à la transformation numérique, l’intelligence artificielle (IA) et l’automatisation des processus par la robotique (RPA). L’International Data Corporation (IDC) <a class="link"   href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=IDC_P32575"  title="IDC">prévoit <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> que les dépenses mondiales dans ce type de technologies atteindront 1,3 milliard d’USD en 2018 et conserveront un rythme de croissance soutenu au cours des cinq années à venir. De plus, Gartner <a class="link"   href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/top-trends-in-the-gartner-hype-cycle-for-emerging-technologies-2017/"  title="Gartner">considère <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> l’IA comme la catégorie de technologies la plus disruptive qui, au cours des dix prochaines années, apportera aux entreprises un avantage concurrentiel sans précédent. Selon Forrester, le marché de l’IA <a class="link"   href="https://www.forrester.com/report/The+RPA+Market+Will+Reach+29+Billion+By+2021/-/E-RES137229"  title="Forrester">va décupler <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> pour atteindre 29 milliards d’USD d’ici 2020, tandis que le marché de la RPA doublera pour atteindre 2,4 milliards d’USD. McKinsey <a class="link"   href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/digital-mckinsey/our-insights/where-machines-could-replace-humans-and-where-they-cant-yet"  title="McKinsey">prévoit <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> également que d’ici 2036, près de 50 % des processus métiers seront automatisés.</p><p>« Les entreprises comprennent la nécessité de transformer leur processus pour survivre sur les marchés actuels, avec des clients qui ont <em>une réelle exigence d’immédiateté</em>. Les plateformes et solutions d’intelligence artificielle d’ABBYY leur permettent de réussir leur transformation numérique et leur automatisation des processus aussi aisément que possible. C’est pourquoi nous constatons un intérêt croissant pour notre gamme de produits, » commente Ulf Persson, CEO d’ABBYY. « Les entreprises utilisent nos technologies pour accélérer leurs processus d’intégration et de prise de décision, gérer les risques et extraire des informations pertinentes à partir de vastes quantités de données non structurées. »</p><p>En 2017, des changements organisationnels ont également eu lieu au sein d’ABBYY. Ulf Persson a été nommé CEO en janvier 2017, après avoir été Président du conseil d’administration d’ABBYY et y avoir siégé depuis 2002. En tant que CEO, il a créé une nouvelle structure de management mondiale qui, fin 2017, avait intégré les 16 agences implantées dans 13 pays. De nouvelles fonctions ont aussi été créées et un Chief Innovation Officer a été recruté. Ce nouveau modèle répond aux besoins de l’entreprise dans le monde entier, permet de conserver une marque unifiée et renforce la volonté de fournir des innovations dans le domaine de l’intelligence de contenu pour le marché de la transformation numérique.</p><p><strong>A propos d’ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY est un acteur majeur au niveau mondial pour les technologies et les solutions permettant aux entreprises d’actionner l’information. Notre entreprise définit les standards de la capture de données à l’aide de technologies innovantes reposant sur la linguistique et s’intégrant à l’ensemble du cycle de vie des informations. Les solutions ABBYY permettent d’optimiser les processus commerciaux, d’atténuer les risques, d’accélérer les prises de décision et d’accroître les revenus. Les technologies ABBYY sont utilisées sous licence par certaines des plus grandes entreprises et agences gouvernementales internationales, de même que par des PME et des particuliers. ABBYY Europe GmbH est membre du groupe ABBYY et gère les activités commerciales et marketing en Europe occidentale. Le groupe ABBYY dispose de bureaux en Allemagne, au Royaume-Uni, en France, en Espagne, en Ukraine, à Chypre, en Russie, aux États-Unis, au Canada, aux Émirats Arabes Unis, en Australie, au Japon et à Taïwan. Pour en savoir plus, consultez le site <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/"  title="ABBYY">www.ABBYY.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><em>ABBYY, le logo d’ABBYY et FineReader sont des marques déposées ou des appellations commerciales d’ABBYY Software Ltd. Toutes les autres appellations commerciales appartiennent à leurs propriétaires respectifs.</em></p><p><strong>Pour tout renseignement complémentaire, veuillez contacter :</strong></p><p><strong>ABBYY Europe GmbH</strong><br>Eva-Maria Stanglmayr<br>Landsberger Str. 300<br>80687 Munich, Allemagne<br>Tél : +49 89 69 33 33 0<br>Fax : +49 89 69 33 33 300<br>E-mail : press_<a class="link"   href="mailto:&#x65;&#x75;&#x40;&#97;&#x62;&#98;&#121;&#x79;&#x2e;&#x63;&#111;&#109;" >&#x65;&#x75;&#x40;&#97;&#x62;&#98;&#121;&#x79;&#x2e;&#x63;&#111;&#109; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br>Web : <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><strong>Axicom pour ABBYY</strong><br>Agathe Boyé<br>Tél : +33 1 56 02 68 27<br>E-mail : <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >agathe.boye@axicom.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>Maëva Morais<br>Tél : +33 1 56 02 68 26<br>E-mail : <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Maeva.morais@axicom.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a class="link"   href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4729642&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1" >Advanced Find and Replace for Google Sheets, Lifetime subscription <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;How-ABBYY-Achieved-a-Remarkable-25-Increase-in-Revenue-for-the-Year-2N-2017&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#How-ABBYY-Achieved-a-Remarkable-25-Increase-i</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Experience Tailored Browsing - Optimized Using Advanced Cookiebot Solutions</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/experience-tailored-browsing-optimized-using-advanced-cookiebot-solutions/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/experience-tailored-browsing-optimized-using-advanced-cookiebot-solutions/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.816Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.816Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Experience-Tailored-Browsing-Optimized-Using-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions"><a href="#Experience-Tailored-Browsing-Optimized-Using-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions" class="headerlink" title="Experience Tailored Browsing - Optimized Using Advanced Cookiebot Solutions"></a>Experience Tailored Browsing - Optimized Using Advanced Cookiebot Solutions</h2><p>Télécharger la brochure</p><h2 id="5-etapes-pour-reussir-la-mise-en-oeuvre-d’un-projet-RPA-avec-la-Process-Intelligence"><a href="#5-etapes-pour-reussir-la-mise-en-oeuvre-d’un-projet-RPA-avec-la-Process-Intelligence" class="headerlink" title="5 étapes pour réussir la mise en œuvre d’un projet RPA avec la Process Intelligence"></a>5 étapes pour réussir la mise en œuvre d’un projet RPA avec la Process Intelligence</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34494/10c-5-steps-to-successful-rpa-fr-262x340.png"                      alt="Five Steps to Successful RPA Implementation with Process Intelligence PDF - ABBYY Brochure"                ></p><h3 id="Sachant-que-pres-de-la-moitie-des-initiatives-de-RPA-echouent-comment-pouvez-vous-vous-assurer-de-reussir"><a href="#Sachant-que-pres-de-la-moitie-des-initiatives-de-RPA-echouent-comment-pouvez-vous-vous-assurer-de-reussir" class="headerlink" title="Sachant que près de la moitié des initiatives de RPA échouent, comment pouvez-vous vous assurer de réussir?"></a>Sachant que près de la moitié des initiatives de RPA échouent, comment pouvez-vous vous assurer de réussir?</h3><p>Cette brochure explique les raisons pour lesquelles le succès d’un projet de RPA ne dépend pas uniquement du fournisseur de solutions. Alors que l’automatisation devient incontournable pour rationaliser les processus et améliorer l’efficacité, les entreprises doivent prendre en compte de nombreux éléments lorsqu’elles entament leur projet d’automatisation des processus.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.dbschema.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=19867419&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"> <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/176b22bab4e94a28619ca2433b2ef241/products/1_icon256.png"                      border="0"                ><br>DbSchema database designer for all databases, schema design in the team, schema deployment, interactive diagrams, documentation, data and query tools. </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Telecharger-maintenant"><a href="#Telecharger-maintenant" class="headerlink" title="Télécharger maintenant!"></a>Télécharger maintenant!</h3><p>La plateforme de Process Intelligence ABBYY Timeline complète les technologies numériques pour garantir l’excellence des processus. Découvrez les cinq meilleures pratiques à suivre pour une automatisation réussie :</p><p>Augmentez votre Process Intelligence pour une automatisation réellement intelligente</p><p>ABBYY Timeline garantit une mise en œuvre harmonieuse du projet RPA, conduisant à la réingénierie des processus opérationnels. Ceci vous permet à la fois de gagner du temps et de l’argent dans le cadre de votre projet de transformation numérique.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://electronicx.pxf.io/c/5597632/1872496/14483" target="_top" id="1872496"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/14483-1872496"                      border="0" alt="" width="750" height="625"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1872496/14483"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Merci-de-votre-interet-pour-ABBYY"><a href="#Merci-de-votre-interet-pour-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Merci de votre intérêt pour ABBYY."></a>Merci de votre intérêt pour ABBYY.</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://digital.abbyy.com/hubfs/documents/content/brochure-timeline-rpa-5-steps-to-success-fr.pdf"  title="Lire la brochure">Lire la brochure <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://aligracehair.sjv.io/c/5597632/2087267/19272" target="_top" id="2087267"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/19272-2087267"                      border="0" alt="" width="728" height="90"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2087267/19272"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Vous-avez-des-questions-Contactez-ABBYY"><a href="#Vous-avez-des-questions-Contactez-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Vous avez des questions ? Contactez ABBYY"></a>Vous avez des questions ? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contactez ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form"><a href="#Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form" class="headerlink" title="Get your copy by filling in the form."></a>Get your copy by filling in the form.</h4><p>Prénom*</p><p>Nom de famille*</p><p>Courriel*</p><p>Pays*</p><p>PaysAfghanistanÎles d’ÅlandAlbanieAlgérieSamoa américainesAndorreAngolaAnguillaAntarctiqueAntigua-et-BarbudaArgentineArménieArubaAustralieAutricheAzerbaïdjanBahamasBahreïnBangladeshBarbadeBelgiqueBelizeBéninBermudesBhoutanBolivieBonaire, Saint-Eustache et SabaBosnie-HerzégovineBotswanaÎle BouvetBrésilTerritoire britannique de l’océan IndienÎles Vierges britanniquesBrunéi DarussalamBulgarieBurkina FasoBurundiCambodgeCamerounCanadaCabo VerdeÎles CaïmanesRépublique centrafricaineTchadChiliChineÎle ChristmasÎles des Cocos (Keeling)ColombieComoresCongoRépublique démocratique du CongoÎles CookCosta RicaCroatieCuraçaoChypreTchéquieCôte d’IvoireDanemarkDjiboutiDominiqueRépublique dominicaineÉquateurÉgypteEl SalvadorGuinée équatorialeÉrythréeEstonieÉthiopieÎles Falkland (Malvinas)Îles FéroéFidjiFinlandeFranceGuyane françaisePolynésie françaiseTerres australes françaisesGabonGambieGéorgieAllemagneGhanaGibraltarGrèceGroenlandGrenadeGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuerneseyGuinéeGuinée-BissauGuyanaHaïtiÎle Heard-et-Îles MacDonaldSaint-SiègeHondurasHong KongHongrieIslandeIndeIndonésieIraqIrlandeÎle de ManIsraëlITJamaïqueJaponJerseyJordanieKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiRépublique de CoréeKoweïtKyrgyzstanLaosLettonieLibanLesothoLibériaLibyeLiechtensteinLituanieLuxembourgMacaoex-République yougoslave de MacédoineMadagascarMalawiMalaisieMaldivesMaliMalteÎles MarshallMartiniqueMauritanieMauriceMayotteMexiqueMicronésieRépublique de MoldovaMonacoMongolieMonténégroMontserratMarocMozambiqueMyanmarNamibieNauruNépalPays-BasAntilles NéerlandaisesNouvelle-CalédonieNouvelle-ZélandeNicaraguaNigerNigériaNiouéÎle NorfolkÎles Mariannes du NordNorvègeOmanPakistanPalaosÉtat de PalestinePanamaPapouasie-Nouvelle-GuinéeParaguayPérouPhilippinesPitcairnPolognePortugalPorto RicoQatarRoumanieRwandaRéunionSainte-HélèneSaint-Kitts-et-NevisSainte-LucieSaint-Pierre-et-MiquelonSaint-Vincent-et-les GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (partie française)SamoaSaint-MarinSao Tomé-et-PrincipeArabie saouditeSénégalSerbieSeychellesSierra LeoneSingapourSaint-Martin (partie néerlandaise)SlovaquieSlovénieÎles SalomonAfrique du SudGéorgie du Sud-et-les Îles Sandwich du SudSoudan du SudEspagneSri LankaSurinameÎles Svalbard-et-Jan MayenSwazilandSuèdeSuisseTaïwanTadjikistanTanzanieThaïlandeTimor-LesteTogoTokélaouTongaTrinité-et-TobagoTunisieTurquieÎles Turques-et-CaïquesTuvaluOugandaUkraineÉmirats arabes unisRoyaume-UniÉtats-Unis d’AmériqueUruguayÎles mineures éloignées des États-UnisOuzbékistanVanuatuVenezuelaViet NamÎles Vierges américainesÎles Wallis-et-FutunaSahara occidentalZambieZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>J’ai lu et j’accepte la <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Politique relative à la vie privée <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> et la <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Politique relative aux cookies <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>J’accepte de recevoir des e-mails d’ABBYY Solutions Ltd., des actualités concernant leur produits et technologies, des invitations à des événements et webinaires, des informations sur les livres blancs et tout contenu lié aux produits et services ABBYY Solutions Ltd..</p></li></ul><p>J’ai été informé que je peux retirer mon consentement à tout moment en cliquant sur le lien de désabonnement se trouvant dans tout email reçu d’ABBYY Solutions Ltd. ou en utilisant le <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >formulaire Droits d’accès aux données personnelles d’ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Salutation</p><p>Academic Title</p><p>Query string</p><p>Posez une question ou décrivez votre demande </p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>City</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Experience-Tailored-Browsing-Optimized-Using-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Experience-Tailored-Browsing-Optimized-Using-Ad</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enhanced User Experience with Automated Tracking: Powered by Cookiebot Technology</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhanced-user-experience-with-automated-tracking-powered-by-cookiebot-technology/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhanced-user-experience-with-automated-tracking-powered-by-cookiebot-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.808Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.808Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Enhanced-User-Experience-with-Automated-Tracking-Powered-by-Cookiebot-Technology"><a href="#Enhanced-User-Experience-with-Automated-Tracking-Powered-by-Cookiebot-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Enhanced User Experience with Automated Tracking: Powered by Cookiebot Technology"></a>Enhanced User Experience with Automated Tracking: Powered by Cookiebot Technology</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Webinars <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Transforming-AP-Operations-More-than-Adding-Automation-It-Requires-Content-Intelligence"><a href="#Transforming-AP-Operations-More-than-Adding-Automation-It-Requires-Content-Intelligence" class="headerlink" title="Transforming AP Operations: More than Adding Automation, It Requires Content Intelligence"></a>Transforming AP Operations: More than Adding Automation, It Requires Content Intelligence</h2><p>English</p><h3 id="Featuring"><a href="#Featuring" class="headerlink" title="Featuring"></a>Featuring</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35123/logo-2021-90x27.svg"                      alt="06 Ryanraiker 198X198"                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25110/06-ryanraiker-198x198.png"                      alt="06 Ryanraiker 198X198"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4600114&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.epubor.com/images/drm-removal-feature2.png"                      border="0"                >Any DRM Removal for Mac： Remove DRM from Adobe, Kindle, Sony eReader, Kobo, etc, read your ebooks anywhere.</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Ryan-Raiker"><a href="#Ryan-Raiker" class="headerlink" title="Ryan Raiker"></a>Ryan Raiker</h3><p>Director of Digital Marketing, <strong>ABBYY</strong></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4572700&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.tubedigger.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/tubedigger-software-new.png"                      border="0"                >TubeDigger - online video downloader from mostly any site</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Digital-Intelligence-for-Insurance-Companies-is-a-necessity-in-order-to-understand-processes-data-and-the-future-of-work-for-insurance-providers"><a href="#Digital-Intelligence-for-Insurance-Companies-is-a-necessity-in-order-to-understand-processes-data-and-the-future-of-work-for-insurance-providers" class="headerlink" title="Digital Intelligence for Insurance Companies is a necessity in order to understand processes, data and the future of work for insurance providers?"></a>Digital Intelligence for Insurance Companies is a necessity in order to understand processes, data and the future of work for insurance providers?</h3><p>It’s time for insurance leaders to identify new opportunities, maximize business performance, and make better use of the data they already capture.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4726960&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/5f4f7141b65a730b4efb0e0d51f63e94/products/forexrobotronbox.gif"                      border="0"                >Forex Robotron Basic Package</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="About-this-webinar"><a href="#About-this-webinar" class="headerlink" title="About this webinar"></a>About this webinar</h3><p>Watch our webinar to learn the next generation of resource solutions and the difference-maker for the future of insurance analytics, delivering business value for internal staff, contract adjusters, third-party support organizations, and other insurance partners.</p><ul><li>Build a process control and command center</li><li>100% end-to-end process transparency</li><li>Continuous process improvement</li><li>Predict issues before they happen</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://funwhole.sjv.io/c/5597632/1702887/17189" target="_top" id="1702887"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17189-1702887"                      border="0" alt="" width="1000" height="1000"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1702887/17189"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Fill-in-the-form-to-register-for-the-webinar-now"><a href="#Fill-in-the-form-to-register-for-the-webinar-now" class="headerlink" title="Fill in the form to register for the webinar now"></a>Fill in the form to register for the webinar now</h3><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.mondly.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=ATISTUDI&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mondly.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3D%2BEducational%2B300x600%2B"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/69c418c33ec2e1a4267fa9bb77fa1428/educational-300x600.gif"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Get-in-touch-with-us"><a href="#Get-in-touch-with-us" class="headerlink" title="Get in touch with us"></a>Get in touch with us</h3><p>Please note that progressive profiling is used on this form to incrementally collect profile data over time.<br>All personal information collected via this method is under full scope of all provisions in our privacy policy.</p><h2 id="�Thank-you-enjoy-your-webinar"><a href="#�Thank-you-enjoy-your-webinar" class="headerlink" title="�Thank you, enjoy your webinar."></a>�Thank you, enjoy your webinar.</h2><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W3ASxg1rfik"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25549/03-diforinsurance.jpg"                      alt="03 Diforinsurance"                ></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2087389/7443" target="_top" id="2087389"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2087389"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2087389/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><h4 id="Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY"><a href="#Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Have questions? Contact ABBYY"></a>Have questions? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar"><a href="#Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar" class="headerlink" title="Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:"></a>Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:</h4><p>First name*</p><p>Last name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Phone</p><p>Company*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Query string</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Enhanced-User-Experience-with-Automated-Tracking-Powered-by-Cookiebot-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Enhanced-User-Experience-with-Automated-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enhanced Personalization with the Latest Cookiebot Technology</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhanced-personalization-with-the-latest-cookiebot-technology/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhanced-personalization-with-the-latest-cookiebot-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.800Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.800Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Enhanced-Personalization-with-the-Latest-Cookiebot-Technology"><a href="#Enhanced-Personalization-with-the-Latest-Cookiebot-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Enhanced Personalization with the Latest Cookiebot Technology"></a>Enhanced Personalization with the Latest Cookiebot Technology</h2><h2 id="Clayton-C-Peddy"><a href="#Clayton-C-Peddy" class="headerlink" title="Clayton C. Peddy"></a>Clayton C. Peddy</h2><p>Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/company/management/headshots/cards-headshots/743x418_clayton_peddy.jpg?h=418&iar=0&w=743"                      alt="743x418_Clayton_Peddy"                ></p><h4 id="Clayton-C-Peddy-is-the-Chief-Information-Security-Officer-CISO-at-ABBYY-He-brings-over-two-decades-of-experience-in-cybersecurity-technology-leadership-and-software-development-Clayton-has-held-key-roles-in-leading-industry-players-such-as-OutSystems-and-Citrix"><a href="#Clayton-C-Peddy-is-the-Chief-Information-Security-Officer-CISO-at-ABBYY-He-brings-over-two-decades-of-experience-in-cybersecurity-technology-leadership-and-software-development-Clayton-has-held-key-roles-in-leading-industry-players-such-as-OutSystems-and-Citrix" class="headerlink" title="Clayton C. Peddy is the Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at ABBYY. He brings over two decades of experience in cybersecurity, technology leadership, and software development. Clayton has held key roles in leading industry players such as OutSystems and Citrix."></a>Clayton C. Peddy is the Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at ABBYY. He brings over two decades of experience in cybersecurity, technology leadership, and software development. Clayton has held key roles in leading industry players such as OutSystems and Citrix.</h4><p>With a strong background in computer science, Clayton spearheads the implementation of secure development lifecycle frameworks, driving significant improvements in efficiency and compliance remediation. As the CISO of ABBYY, Clayton leads the company’s information security initiatives, reinforcing its commitment to maintaining the highest standards of data protection, regulatory compliance, and innovation for its customers and partners.</p><p>Beyond his professional endeavors, Clayton is a published author and sought-after speaker in the cybersecurity and technology space. He has served as a Computer Science Industry Board Member at California State University, Chico and is a regular youth volunteer, further demonstrating his commitment to the field and his contributions to education and industry development.</p><h3 id="Ready-to-speak-with-an-expert"><a href="#Ready-to-speak-with-an-expert" class="headerlink" title="Ready to speak with an expert?"></a>Ready to speak with an expert?</h3><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Schedule a demo <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Get in touch <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4726807&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/c14a8df1e1b4d5297e9cb30cb34d5a00/products/copy_copy_power-tools-48.png"                      border="0"                >Power Tools add-on for Google Sheets, Lifetime subscription</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Enhanced-Personalization-with-the-Latest-Cookiebot-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Enhanced-Personalization-with-the-Latest-Cookiebot-Technolo</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enhance Your Site&#39;s User Experience with the Advanced Capabilities of Cookiebot Technology</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhance-your-sites-user-experience-with-the-advanced-capabilities-of-cookiebot-technology/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhance-your-sites-user-experience-with-the-advanced-capabilities-of-cookiebot-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.796Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.796Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Enhance-Your-Site’s-User-Experience-with-the-Advanced-Capabilities-of-Cookiebot-Technology"><a href="#Enhance-Your-Site’s-User-Experience-with-the-Advanced-Capabilities-of-Cookiebot-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Enhance Your Site’s User Experience with the Advanced Capabilities of Cookiebot Technology"></a>Enhance Your Site’s User Experience with the Advanced Capabilities of Cookiebot Technology</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Understanding-the-intrinsic-value-of-documents"><a href="#Understanding-the-intrinsic-value-of-documents" class="headerlink" title="Understanding the intrinsic value of documents"></a>Understanding the intrinsic value of documents</h2><p>September 07, 2017</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25229/cropblog_0709.png"                      alt="Understanding the intrinsic value of documents | ABBYY Blog Post"                > </p><p>We have all done it. Spent ages looking for that one document, with the name of that guy from the company with a funny name. Was it an email, a PowerPoint presentation or a PDF?</p><p>Why do we search for documents in the first place? Usually it is to discover what information resides <em>inside</em> the document. But if we already have the document, shouldn’t we already know what it contains?</p><h2 id="Information-buried-inside-documents"><a href="#Information-buried-inside-documents" class="headerlink" title="Information buried inside documents"></a>Information buried inside documents</h2><p>The key question is not how much time we spending searching for documents, but <em>why</em> we are searching for them in the first place. The answer is simple, buried inside these elusive documents is business critical information. The information is unstructured and, in many cases analogue, e.g. a scanned image of a textual document rather than a digital file containing text.</p><p>Rather than searching for a document in response to some event, surely it makes sense to act on the information the moment that it comes into our possession.</p><p>This necessitates that the document be searched for, retrieved and read in order to extract the information it contains. This is both time consuming and expensive.</p><p>Optical Character Recognition technologies have been with us for decades, what is now required is something that can rapidly, cost-effectively and <em>intelligently</em> extract structured business information from these documents.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.revouninstaller.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=28010250&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/4282ec8de8c9be897e7aff4aa231b1a4/336__280a.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Improving-the-total-customer-experience"><a href="#Improving-the-total-customer-experience" class="headerlink" title="Improving the total customer experience"></a>Improving the total customer experience</h2><p>If we have immediate access to this business information, we can act on it the moment it is received. This ensures that organizations can provide the fastest and most appropriate response to customer interactions.</p><p>For example, rather than replying to a customer email inquiry with a default response stating that:</p><p>We will respond to your request in 3-4 business days.</p><p>Imagine the improvement in the customers experience if the response automatically, and immediately, provides information helping to address the customer’s issue.</p><p>Furthermore, by understanding the content of the inquiry it would be possible to automatically identify those issues which are high priority and escalate them accordingly.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://funwhole.sjv.io/c/5597632/1702887/17189" target="_top" id="1702887"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17189-1702887"                      border="0" alt="" width="1000" height="1000"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1702887/17189"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Accelerating-business-transactions-and-creating-new-revenue-streams"><a href="#Accelerating-business-transactions-and-creating-new-revenue-streams" class="headerlink" title="Accelerating business transactions and creating new revenue streams"></a>Accelerating business transactions and creating new revenue streams</h2><p>Having the ability to process unstructured information and transforming it into actionable business data, strips away the inherent latency in business operations. This accelerate business transactions and optimizes successful business outcomes.</p><p>The insight provided into these interactions can also help identify potential new revenue streams, by providing a level of analytics inaccessible if the information were to remain locked away, bereft of structure, inside isolated pieces of content.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://coinrule.sjv.io/c/5597632/1958379/18409" target="_top" id="1958379"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18409-1958379"                      border="0" alt="" width="856" height="508"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1958379/18409"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Accounts-payable"><a href="#Accounts-payable" class="headerlink" title="Accounts payable"></a>Accounts payable</h2><p>Every business deals with Accounts Payable. Many small businesses view the accounting function as a necessary evil, but it is the prompt payment of invoices that literally keeps you, and your suppliers, in business.</p><p>Invoices are an example of documents containing critical business information, which often needs to be entered into software applications in order to facilitate payment. This requires a user to read the invoice and enter the data contained within it into the relevant systems in order to initiate payment.</p><p>Invoices, while containing much of the same business information, can look very different. What is needed is the ability to not only recognize the machine- (and sometimes hand-) printed characters on the page, but the capability to classify the document as an invoice. Once the document is classified as an invoice, the data contained within it needs to be identified, extracted and passed (along with the captured image) to both the appropriate Financial software applications and ECM repository.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.manycam.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=17728032&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/8230bea7d54bcdf99cdfe85cb07313d5/mcaffbanner920x120.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Putting-business-information-to-work"><a href="#Putting-business-information-to-work" class="headerlink" title="Putting business information to work"></a>Putting business information to work</h2><p>The solution is to integrate capture technologies with embedded AI (Artificial Intelligence) to autonomously classify documents, extract the desired business critical information and seamlessly pass the captured documents along with their accompanying extracted <em>structured</em> business information to ECM, ERP and BPM applications.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Digital Transformation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Accounts Payable Automation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Finance &amp; Accounting <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://otszone.ots7.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4713321&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://green.ots7.com/screenshots/OtsAV/OtsAVDJ1.90-300x188.jpg"                      border="0"                >OtsAV DJ Pro</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Enhance-Your-Site’s-User-Experience-with-the-Advanced-Capabilities-of-Cookiebot-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Enhance-Your-Site’s-User-Exper</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enhance Website Traffic with the Power of Cookiebot Technology</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhance-website-traffic-with-the-power-of-cookiebot-technology/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhance-website-traffic-with-the-power-of-cookiebot-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.785Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.785Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Enhance-Website-Traffic-with-the-Power-of-Cookiebot-Technology"><a href="#Enhance-Website-Traffic-with-the-Power-of-Cookiebot-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Enhance Website Traffic with the Power of Cookiebot Technology"></a>Enhance Website Traffic with the Power of Cookiebot Technology</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Zurück zu den Kundenreferenzen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>BPO and Shared Services | Digital Archiving</p><h2 id="RWS-setzt-auf-die-Vorteile-von-ABBYY-Recognition-Server"><a href="#RWS-setzt-auf-die-Vorteile-von-ABBYY-Recognition-Server" class="headerlink" title="RWS setzt auf die Vorteile von ABBYY Recognition Server"></a>RWS setzt auf die Vorteile von ABBYY Recognition Server</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/de/70290.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Zurück zu den Kundenreferenzen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="RWS-setzt-auf-die-Vorteile-von-ABBYY-Recognition-Server-1"><a href="#RWS-setzt-auf-die-Vorteile-von-ABBYY-Recognition-Server-1" class="headerlink" title="RWS setzt auf die Vorteile von ABBYY Recognition Server"></a>RWS setzt auf die Vorteile von ABBYY Recognition Server</h2><p>BPO&#x2F;Dienstleistung­sanbieter | Digitale Archivierung </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14330/3-rws_rs_e.jpg"                                     > </p><h4 id="Uber-den-Kunden"><a href="#Uber-den-Kunden" class="headerlink" title="Über den Kunden"></a>Über den Kunden</h4><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14444/rws.jpg"                      alt="RWS Group"                > </p><table><thead><tr><th>Name</th><th>RWS Group</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Hauptsitz</td><td>Bucks, UK</td></tr><tr><td>Branche</td><td>Patentübersetzungen und Recherchen</td></tr><tr><td>Mitarbeiter</td><td>350</td></tr><tr><td>Website</td><td><a class="link"   href="http://www.rws.com/" >www.rws.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></td></tr></tbody></table><h6 id="Herausforderung"><a href="#Herausforderung" class="headerlink" title="Herausforderung"></a>Herausforderung</h6><p>Eine effiziente Lösung für die digitale Archivierung von Millionen von Dokumenten wurde gesucht.</p><h6 id="Losung"><a href="#Losung" class="headerlink" title="Lösung"></a>Lösung</h6><p>Automatisierte Dokumentenumwandlung in durchsuchbare PDF-Dateien und Zuweisung von Metadaten für EMC Documentum.</p><h6 id="Ergebnis"><a href="#Ergebnis" class="headerlink" title="Ergebnis"></a>Ergebnis</h6><ul><li>Rascher ROI in weniger als 12 Monaten</li><li>Kostenersparnis von 100.000 GBP</li><li>Hoch-skalierbare Lösung</li><li>Voll durchsuchbare Archive</li></ul><p>RWS wird als einer der weltführenden Rechercheservices- und Übersetzungsunternehmen für Patente gehandelt. Die Klientel befindet sich hauptsächlich im Ingenieurwesen, der Chemie- und Pharmaindustrie und dem Rechtswesen. Das Unternehmen beschäftigt heute 350 Mitarbeiter und betreibt Filialen in Großbritannien, den USA, Japan und Deutschland und hat Verkaufsniederlassungen in Frankreich und in der Schweiz.</p><h4 id="Herausforderung-1"><a href="#Herausforderung-1" class="headerlink" title="Herausforderung"></a>Herausforderung</h4><p>Das Aufgabenfeld von RWS ist sehr dokumentenlastig, jährlich werden Millionen an Seiten bei Übersetzungen für Kunden produziert. Zusätzlich zu der Übersetzung von Patenten kamen in den letzten Jahren immer mehr Aufträge aus anderen Wirtschaftsbereichen hinzu. Dadurch hat RWS seine Aufgaben auf die Übersetzung von längeren Dokumenten wie Gebrauchsanweisungen, Broschüren und Websites ausgeweitet.</p><p>Normalerweise speichert RWS seine Dokumente als mehrseitige TIF Bilddateien. 2007 hat die Firma aber entschieden, dass diese Speichermethode nicht länger ausreichte. Um besser mit den Dokumenten arbeiten zu können, benötigte RWS eine Software, die die Scans der neu übersetzten Dokumente in durchsuchbare PDF-Dateien umwandeln und diese dann in ein digitales Archiv einordnen konnte. Es war RWS stets ein Anliegen, die richtigen Technologien zu finden, die das Unternehmen bei seinem Geschäftsalltag optimal unterstützen. Mit diesem Vorsatz machte man sich ebenfalls auf die Suche nach der besten Lösung für die Verarbeitung des großen Dokumentenaufkommens.</p><h4 id="Herausforderungen-gemeinsam-meistern-wie-kann-ABBYY-Sie-unterstutzen"><a href="#Herausforderungen-gemeinsam-meistern-wie-kann-ABBYY-Sie-unterstutzen" class="headerlink" title="Herausforderungen gemeinsam meistern - wie kann ABBYY Sie unterstützen?"></a>Herausforderungen gemeinsam meistern - wie kann ABBYY Sie unterstützen?</h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="Losung-1"><a href="#Losung-1" class="headerlink" title="Lösung"></a>Lösung</h4><p>Nach sorgfältigen Überlegungen und eingehenden Gesprächen empfahl ABBYY dem Unternehmen Recognition Server. Recognition Server ist eine robuste und leistungsstarke serverbasierte Lösung, die speziell für die Umwandlung von mittleren bis großen Mengen an Dokumenten entwickelt wurde und die auch abteilungs- und unternehmensübergreifend einsetzbar ist. Die Software kann sowohl als Standalone als auch als Teilsystem in bereits bestehende Drittsysteme wie DMS, RMS und andere Archivierungssysteme integriert werden. Eine routinemäßige Umwandlung von Dokumenten wird automatisch und unbeaufsichtigt durchgeführt.</p><p>Recognition Server ist ideal als zentralisierter Service für Anwender, die OCR im Unternehmensalltag verwenden, Dokumente in durchsuchbare PDF- und PDF&#x2F;A-Dateien umwandeln sowie digitale Archive oder Protokolle erstellen möchten. Nach der Installation auf einem Server in der Zentrale eines Unternehmens bietet die Lösung rund um die Uhr OCR-Services für alle Mitarbeiter, auch die, die keinen lokalen Zugriff auf das System haben, sondern von zuhause oder von anderen Niederlassungen aus über eine Intranetverbindung arbeiten. Dank der preisgekrönten ABBYY OCR-Technologie ist Recognition Server besonders für die Anwendung in internationalen Umgebungen geeignet und bietet genaueste Texterkennung in mehr als 190 Sprachen.</p><p> „Wir benötigten eine OCR-Anwendung, die mit Leichtigkeit eine Vielzahl an Dateiformaten handhaben konnte. Wir haben ABBYY mit unserem bisherigen OCR-Produkt wie auch mit anderen Anbietern, die wir bis jetzt noch nicht verwendet hatten, verglichen. Was die Anwenderfreundlichkeit, die Präzision und die Geschwindigkeit anbelangt, hat ABBYY die Konkurrenz um Längen hinter sich gelassen. Auch was den Kostenfaktor anbetrifft, der ebenfalls ein wesentlicher Punkt war, lag ABBYY vor den anderen Anbietern. Entscheidend war für uns zudem die Fähigkeit der Lösung, unterschiedliche Workflows in Abhängigkeit von der Sprache der Dokumente aufzusetzen. Recognition Server war das einzige Produkt, das Double-Byte Zeichen, wie sie in Japan und in Korea verwendet werden, korrekt erkennen und zeit- und kosteneffizient umwandeln konnte.“</p><p> Alan Price, RWS Group Technical Manager</p><p>Recognition Server wurde in das RWS-interne System über eine speziell von RWS entwickelte Applikation integriert. Für die Anwender im Unternehmen ist der Vorgang sehr einfach: Dokumente werden mit einem Barcode über eines der bereitstehenden Multifunktionsgeräte eingescannt, eine Applikation legt die Bilddateien in einen Hot Folder, der von Recognition Server überwacht wird und der Rest des Vorgangs verläuft automatisch. Für standardmäßige Anwendungen verarbeitet das System so etwa 5000 Seiten pro Tag.</p><p>Recognition Server verarbeitet jede Bilddatei entsprechend einem Workflow – einer Reihe an Verarbeitungsparametern, die vom Administrator festgelegt werden. Recognition Server kann gleichzeitig mehrere Workflows mit verschiedenen Parametern handhaben, wobei jeder Workflow einer Eingabequelle zugeordnet ist (einem Ordner oder einer Mailbox). Alle Bilddateien, die im jeweiligen Ordner&#x2F;Posteingang abgelegt werden, werden nach dem zugehörigen Workflow bearbeitet. Werden mehrere Workflows eingerichtet, so verarbeitet ABBYY Recognition Server die Dateien aller Workflows gleichzeitig – entsprechend der jeweiligen Erstellungszeit und dem Prioritätslevel.</p><p>Obwohl RWS ursprünglich geplant hatte, Recognition Server nur für die Umwandlung neuer Dokumente zu benutzen, hat das Unternehmen sich entschieden, die Anforderungen an die Software zu erweitern und seine gesamten digitalen Archive in ein neues Format umzuwandeln. Für RWS war dieses kürzlich angelaufene Konvertierungsprojekt ein entscheidender Schritt, um die bisher genutzte Speicherungsmethode durch TIF-Dateien hinter sich zu lassen. Der Plan war, alle vorhandenen Dokumente in durchsuchbare PDF-Dateien umzuwandeln und diese dann zusammen mit den Metadaten in EMC Documentum einzugliedern. Insgesamt wurden 28 Millionen Seiten, die in Formaten wie Word, PDF, TIFF, HTML, JPG, XLS und als CSV-Dateien gespeichert waren, in nur sieben Monaten verarbeitet. Um dies in der zur Verfügung stehenden Zeit erreichen zu können, wurden bei RWS 3500 mehrseitige Dokumente, oder 100.000 Seiten pro Tag verarbeitet.  </p><p> „Das Projekt läuft erfolgreich in den letzten Zügen. Wir sind sehr zufrieden mit der Fähigkeit von Recognition Server, eine solche Menge an Dokumente zu bewältigen und sind begeistert, wie flexibel ABBYY mit den Lizenzen gewesen ist. Als wir eine große Anzahl an Dokumenten in sehr kurzer Zeit verarbeiten mussten, kam uns ABBYY mit einem Angebot für eine spezielle temporäre Lizenz entgegen, die wir zur Steigerung des Durchsatzes für dieses Projekt nutzen konnten.“</p><p> Alan Price, RWS Group Technical Manager</p><h4 id="Ergebnis-1"><a href="#Ergebnis-1" class="headerlink" title="Ergebnis"></a>Ergebnis</h4><p>Die Vorteile für RWS durch Recognition Server sind zahlreich. Recognition Server erlaubt es RWS, all seine Dokumente als durchsuchbare PDF-Dateien zu speichern, sodass sie den Anwendern durchgehend und zuverlässig zur Verfügung gestellt werden können. Durch die Speicherung der Dokumente als durchsuchbare PDF-Dateien kann RWS jedes Dokument in ein DMS eingliedern und somit für die interne Recherche bereit stellen.</p><p>„Die Installation der Software verlief schnell und reibungslos, ohne dass zusätzliche Hilfe von außen benötigt worden wäre“, hebt Alan Price von RWS hervor. „Und das Beste ist, dass wir praktisch kein Anwendertraining durchführen mussten, da sich die Angestellten in kürzester Zeit auf das neue System umstellen konnten.“</p><p>Der ROI für die erste Recognition Server Installation konnte bereits nach 12 Monaten erzielt werden. Zudem schätzt RWS die ersten Kosteneinsparungen auf etwa 100.000 Pfund, die Hälfte davon bedingt durch geringeren Arbeitsaufwand, der Rest entstanden durch verschiedene Faktoren wie geringere Lizenzgebühren. Die Skalierbarkeit von Recognition Server hat es RWS ermöglicht, die Nutzung der Dokumentenumwandlung auch auf andere Bereiche des Unternehmens zu erweitern. Die Lösung passt sich dem Wachstum des Unternehmens an und bietet automatisierte Verarbeitung auch bei steigenden Anforderungen.</p><p> „Unsere Dokumente waren immer in einem durchsuchbaren Format abgespeichert, doch durchsuchbare PDF-Dateien sind weitaus praktischer als mehrseitige TIF Dateien. Da wir die Dokumente nun als PDFs speichern können, sind wir wesentlich zuversichtlicher, was die Nachhaltigkeit unseres Archivs anbelangt“, erklärt Alan Price von RWS. „Wir haben unsere internen Prozesse optimiert, was es uns ermöglicht unseren Kunden einen schnelleren und besseren Service anzubieten. Recognition Server war und ist ein beständiger Gewinn für unser Unternehmen.“</p><p> Alan Price, RWS Group Technical Manager</p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/20638/11-frs-casepreview.jpg"                      alt="ABBYY Recognition Server wird jetzt ABBYY FineReader Server genannt"                ></a> “) <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Recognition Server (jetzt FineReader Server genannt) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> “) </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Mehr erfahren <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> “) </p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14364/14-bpo.jpg"                      alt="14-bpo"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >BPOs und Outsourcing-Dienstleister <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Mehr erfahren <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/6145/cs%5Frws%5Frs%5Fd.pdf" title="PDF-Version"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14329/3a-rws_rs_e_small.jpg"                      alt="3a-rws_rs_e_small"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/6145/cs%5Frws%5Frs%5Fd.pdf"  title="PDF-Version">PDF-Version <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/6145/cs%5Frws%5Frs%5Fd.pdf"  title="PDF-Version">Zum Dokument <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h6 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h6><p>Teilen  True ?  : “” </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Mehr über ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Alle ABBYY-Niederlassungen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://atezr.pxf.io/c/5597632/2018605/18496" target="_top" id="2018605"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18496-2018605"                      border="0" alt="" width="798" height="807"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2018605/18496"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Sind-Sie-bereit-mit-einem-Experten-zu-sprechen"><a href="#Sind-Sie-bereit-mit-einem-Experten-zu-sprechen" class="headerlink" title="Sind Sie bereit, mit einem Experten zu sprechen?"></a>Sind Sie bereit, mit einem Experten zu sprechen?</h3><p>Wir würden Sie gerne auf Ihrem Weg zur Automatisierung unterstützen.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Enhance-Website-Traffic-with-the-Power-of-Cookiebot-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Enhance-Website-Traffic-with-the-Power-of-Cookiebot-Techno</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enhance User Experience and Conversions Using the Latest in Cookiebot Analytics Tools</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhance-user-experience-and-conversions-using-the-latest-in-cookiebot-analytics-tools/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/enhance-user-experience-and-conversions-using-the-latest-in-cookiebot-analytics-tools/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.773Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.773Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Enhance-User-Experience-and-Conversions-Using-the-Latest-in-Cookiebot-Analytics-Tools"><a href="#Enhance-User-Experience-and-Conversions-Using-the-Latest-in-Cookiebot-Analytics-Tools" class="headerlink" title="Enhance User Experience and Conversions Using the Latest in Cookiebot Analytics Tools"></a>Enhance User Experience and Conversions Using the Latest in Cookiebot Analytics Tools</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Webinars <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Don’t-Miss-the-Intelligent-Process-Automation-IPA-Opportunity"><a href="#Don’t-Miss-the-Intelligent-Process-Automation-IPA-Opportunity" class="headerlink" title="Don’t Miss the Intelligent Process Automation (IPA) Opportunity"></a>Don’t Miss the Intelligent Process Automation (IPA) Opportunity</h2><p>English</p><h3 id="Featuring-guest-speaker"><a href="#Featuring-guest-speaker" class="headerlink" title="Featuring guest speaker"></a>Featuring guest speaker</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34150/idc-new-logo-forcards.png"                      alt="104 Neilward Dutton 198X198"                > </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35499/104-neilward-dutton-198x198.png"                      alt="104 Neilward Dutton 198X198"                ></p><h3 id="Neil-Ward-Dutton"><a href="#Neil-Ward-Dutton" class="headerlink" title="Neil Ward-Dutton"></a>Neil Ward-Dutton</h3><p>VP, AI and Intelligent Process Automation European Practices at <strong>IDC</strong></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://vapordna.pxf.io/c/5597632/1494880/17238" target="_top" id="1494880"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17238-1494880"                      border="0" alt="" width="728" height="90"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1494880/17238"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Overview"><a href="#Overview" class="headerlink" title="Overview"></a>Overview</h3><p>The market for IPA is growing. It improves businesses and allows your employees to focus on more rewarding work. Plus, it increases flexibility and drives better business outcomes. The tricky part is not being blinded by the possible benefits. When technology offers so much, you need to narrow your focus. You must figure out where IPA can best help your business.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tb6M81U8rcQ" > <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tb6M81U8rcQ"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35600/preview-dont-miss-the-ipa-opportunity-643x363.jpg"                      alt="Don&#39;t miss the IPA opportunity webinar"                ></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://estore.winxdvd.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4081991&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.winxdvd.com/affiliate/new-banner/wt-500x500.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p>In this webinar, IDC’s Neil Ward Dutton walks you through IPA. This includes the past, present, and future of the technology. He also shows the results of a new IDC Intelligent Automation survey. Check it out now to learn where you stand with the IPA opportunity. Plus, get recommendations on how to maximize ROI with Intelligent Document Processing and Process Mining.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2068411/7443" target="_top" id="2068411"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2068411"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2068411/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Watch-now"><a href="#Watch-now" class="headerlink" title="Watch now"></a>Watch now</h3><h3 id="Get-in-touch-with-us"><a href="#Get-in-touch-with-us" class="headerlink" title="Get in touch with us"></a>Get in touch with us</h3><p>Please note that progressive profiling is used on this form to incrementally collect profile data over time.<br>All personal information collected via this method is under full scope of all provisions in our privacy policy.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://printrendy.pxf.io/c/5597632/1453720/17020" target="_top" id="1453720"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17020-1453720"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1453720/17020"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Thank-you-enjoy-your-webinar"><a href="#Thank-you-enjoy-your-webinar" class="headerlink" title="Thank you, enjoy your webinar!"></a>Thank you, enjoy your webinar!</h2><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mld41Nk9bHc"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35600/preview-dont-miss-the-ipa-opportunity-643x363.jpg"                      alt="Preview Don&#39;t Miss The Ipa Opportunity 643X363"                ></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://caperobbin.sjv.io/c/5597632/2006123/18460" target="_top" id="2006123"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18460-2006123"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2006123/18460"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.nero.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=22889392&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="http://webstatic.nero.com/nero2015-com-wAssets/img/affiliate/media/banner728-90eng.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY"><a href="#Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Have questions? Contact ABBYY"></a>Have questions? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar"><a href="#Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar" class="headerlink" title="Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:"></a>Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:</h4><p>First name*</p><p>Last name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Phone</p><p>Company*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Query string</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Enhance-User-Experience-and-Conversions-Using-the-Latest-in-Cookiebot-Analytics-Tools&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Enhance-User-Experience-and-Convers</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Cookiebot-Enhanced: Unleashing Personalized User Experiences with Cutting-Edge Cookies</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/cookiebot-enhanced-unleashing-personalized-user-experiences-with-cutting-edge-cookies/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/cookiebot-enhanced-unleashing-personalized-user-experiences-with-cutting-edge-cookies/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.764Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.764Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Cookiebot-Enhanced-Unleashing-Personalized-User-Experiences-with-Cutting-Edge-Cookies"><a href="#Cookiebot-Enhanced-Unleashing-Personalized-User-Experiences-with-Cutting-Edge-Cookies" class="headerlink" title="Cookiebot-Enhanced: Unleashing Personalized User Experiences with Cutting-Edge Cookies"></a>Cookiebot-Enhanced: Unleashing Personalized User Experiences with Cutting-Edge Cookies</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-Timeline-5-0-neue-Task-Mining-Fahigkeiten-verbinden-Menschen-Prozesse-und-Inhalte"><a href="#ABBYY-Timeline-5-0-neue-Task-Mining-Fahigkeiten-verbinden-Menschen-Prozesse-und-Inhalte" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Timeline 5.0: neue Task Mining-Fähigkeiten verbinden Menschen, Prozesse und Inhalte"></a>ABBYY Timeline 5.0: neue Task Mining-Fähigkeiten verbinden Menschen, Prozesse und Inhalte</h2><p>13. Oktober 2020</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><h4 id="Die-aktualisierte-Plattform-liefert-eine-360-Grad-Sicht-auf-Betriebsablaufe-indem-sie-Benutzerinteraktionen-mit-Geschaftsprozessen-verknupft-um-datengestutzte-Geschaftsentscheidungen-zu-ermoglichen"><a href="#Die-aktualisierte-Plattform-liefert-eine-360-Grad-Sicht-auf-Betriebsablaufe-indem-sie-Benutzerinteraktionen-mit-Geschaftsprozessen-verknupft-um-datengestutzte-Geschaftsentscheidungen-zu-ermoglichen" class="headerlink" title="Die aktualisierte Plattform liefert eine 360-Grad-Sicht auf Betriebsabläufe, indem sie Benutzerinteraktionen mit Geschäftsprozessen verknüpft, um datengestützte Geschäftsentscheidungen zu ermöglichen"></a><em>Die aktualisierte Plattform liefert eine 360-Grad-Sicht auf Betriebsabläufe, indem sie Benutzerinteraktionen mit Geschäftsprozessen verknüpft, um datengestützte Geschäftsentscheidungen zu ermöglichen</em></h4><p>ABBYY, ein Unternehmen für digitale Intelligenz, gab heute die Einführung von Timeline 5.0 bekannt, der einzigen End-to-End-Plattform für Prozessintelligenz, die durch die Kombination von Einblicken in die Arbeitsabläufe von Personen, Prozessen und Inhalten eine 360-Grad-Sicht auf Geschäftsabläufe bietet. Mit der Nutzung der neuen Task Mining-Funktionen und der zum Patent angemeldeten Process Mining-Technologie analysiert Timeline die Interaktionsdaten von Desktop-Benutzern und verknüpft diese nahtlos mit Prozessdetails, die aus Systemereignisdaten gewonnen werden. Dadurch können Unternehmen die betriebliche Effizienz steigern, das Kundenerlebnis verbessern und digitale Transformationsinitiativen beschleunigen. </p><p>Während der COVID-19-Pandemie stießen zwei Drittel (66,7 %) der Unternehmen laut einer globalen <a class="link"   href="https://www.forrester.com/report/Forrester+Infographic+Digital+Process+Automation+At+Scale/-/E-RES160722"  title="Forrester Report">Forrester-Studie <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>[1] auf fehlerhafte Prozesse. Unternehmen haben Mühe, das Potenzial digitaler Transformationsinitiativen voll auszuschöpfen, weil sie keinen Einblick in ihre Geschäftsprozesse haben. Die Hauptursache liegt darin, dass ihre Business Process Management- (BPM), Robotic Process Automation- (RPA) und Process-Mining-Werkzeuge nicht in der Lage sind, variable Prozesse oder individuelle Schritte einzelner Benutzer im Detail zu verstehen.</p><p>“Unsere Process Intelligence-Tools mit den neuen Task Mining-Fähigkeiten ermöglichen es unseren Kunden, ihre Mitarbeiter, Prozesse und Daten in Einklang zu bringen, was für den Erfolg ihrer digitalen Transformationsbemühungen entscheidend ist”, kommentiert Markus Pichler, Sales VP Europe bei ABBYY. “Die Erweiterung der Digital Intelligence-Plattform von ABBYY mit diesen neuen Funktionen unterstützt Unternehmen bei der Umsetzung ihrer Projekte mit RPA, Analyseprozessautomatisierung und intelligenter Dokumentenverarbeitung, Prozesse besser zu identifizieren, zu gestalten, zu implementieren und zu überwachen, um den höchsten ROI zu erzielen.“</p><p>ABBYY Timeline geht über bereits bestehende Ansätze von Process Discovery und Process Mining hinaus, indem es die vollständige Transparenz von Geschäftsprozessen mit Erkenntnissen aus unstrukturierten und halbstrukturierten Inhalten kombiniert, die von ABBYYs marktführendem Content Intelligence-Portfolio geliefert werden. Laut Gartner positioniert sich die Plattform so, dass sie “auf einzigartige Weise inhalts-&#x2F;fallbasierte digitale Transformationsinitiativen adressiert, indem sie eine End-to-End-Sichtbarkeit hochgradig variabler, inhaltszentrierter Prozesse und deren Ausführung bietet, um Herausforderungen zu identifizieren, die Effizienz zu steigern und das Kundenerlebnis zu verbessern”.[2]</p><p>Um einen umfassenden Einblick in die Kerngeschäftsabläufe zu erhalten, <a class="link"   href="https://www.gartner.com/en/documents/3983907/discover-the-differences-and-use-cases-of-process-mining"  title="Gartner Empfehlungen">empfiehlt Gartner <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> Unternehmen, Task Mining und Process Mining als komplementäre Ansätze miteinander zu kombinieren, um “eine bessere Sichtbarkeit und ein besseres Verständnis zu schaffen und so den Erfolg des Mining sowohl auf der Prozess- als auch auf der Aufgabenebene voranzutreiben”.[3] </p><p>Die Task Mining-Funktionen von Timeline 5.0 sind auf Folgendes ausgelegt:</p><ul><li>Die Identifikation zeitraubender, sich wiederholender Tasks für Automatisierung, damit Mitarbeiter sich auf anspruchsvollere Aktivitäten konzentrieren und Führungskräfte datengesteuerte Entscheidungen für Automatisierungsinitiativen treffen können;</li><li>Das Aufdecken von Abweichungen bei der Ausführung von Aufgaben hilft, Schutzmaßnahmen bei der Automatisierung zu aktivieren, die das Risiko von Konformitätsverletzungen mindern;</li><li>Die Kombination von Detailwissen über die Tasks mit den intuitiven Point-and-Click-Prozessanalyse-Tools von Timeline liefern ein einheitliches End-to-End-Betriebsverständnis und stellen sicher, dass digitale Transformationsinitiativen kalkulierbare Ergebnisse liefern und keine unbeabsichtigten Folgen verursachen;</li><li>Die einfache Skalierbarkeit auf eine große Anzahl von Desktop-Benutzern ermöglicht das Aufdecken aller Variationen der Benutzeraktionen während gleichzeitig sensible Informationen durch diverse Datensicherheitsdienste streng geschützt werden.</li></ul><p>Um mehr über ABBYY Timeline 5.0 zu erfahren, besuchen Sie bitte: <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/de/timeline/" >https://www.abbyy.com/de/timeline/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Wenn Sie mehr über ABBYYs umfassendes Angebot an Digital Intelligence-Lösungen zur Transformation von Unternehmensprozessen und -inhalten erfahren möchten, besuchen Sie bitte: <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/de/solutions/digital-intelligence/" >https://www.abbyy.com/de/solutions/digital-intelligence/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>[1] “Forrester Infographic: Digital Process Automation At Scale”, Forrester Research, Inc., July 14, 2020.</p><p>[2] Gartner “Market Guide for Process Mining,” Marc Kerremans, et al, 30 September 2020.</p><p>[3] Gartner “Discover the Differences and Use Cases of Process Mining Versus Task Mining,” Marc Kerremans, Tushar Srivastava, 22 April 2020.</p><p><strong>Über ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY ermöglicht es, mit seiner Digital Intelligence Plattform die gesamten Geschäftsprozesse und Informationen, die ein Unternehmen antreiben, zu analysieren und im Detail zu verstehen. ABBYY-Technologien werden von mehr als 5.000 Unternehmen weltweit eingesetzt, darunter viele Fortune-500-Unternehmen. Die als führend ausgezeichneten Lösungen im Bereich <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Intelligent Document Processing <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> (IDP) und <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Discovery &amp; Mining <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> steigern Effizienz, Rentabilität und Wettbewerbsfähigkeit eines Unternehmens und verbessern das Kundenerlebnis nachhaltig. ABBYY ist ein globales Unternehmen mit Niederlassungen in 13 Ländern. Weitere Informationen finden Sie unter <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >https://www.abbyy.com/de/company/key-facts <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><em>ABBYY und das ABBYY Logo sind entweder registrierte Warenzeichen oder Warenzeichen von ABBYY Software Ltd. Alle anderen Warenzeichen sind Eigentum ihrer jeweiligen Inhaber.</em></p><p><strong>Pressekontakt</strong></p><p>Eva-Maria Hufschmitt, ABBYY</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >eva-maria.hufschmitt@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://uperfect.sjv.io/c/5597632/1246754/15155" target="_top" id="1246754"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/15155-1246754"                      border="0" alt="" width="600" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1246754/15155"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Cookiebot-Enhanced-Unleashing-Personalized-User-Experiences-with-Cutting-Edge-Cookies&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Cookiebot-Enhanced-Unleashing-Perso</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Cookiebot-Enabled Website: Enhance Your Traffic with Smart Tracking</title>
    <link href="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/cookiebot-enabled-website-enhance-your-traffic-with-smart-tracking/"/>
    <id>https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/cookiebot-enabled-website-enhance-your-traffic-with-smart-tracking/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T06:58:58.756Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T06:58:58.756Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Cookiebot-Enabled-Website-Enhance-Your-Traffic-with-Smart-Tracking"><a href="#Cookiebot-Enabled-Website-Enhance-Your-Traffic-with-Smart-Tracking" class="headerlink" title="Cookiebot-Enabled Website: Enhance Your Traffic with Smart Tracking"></a>Cookiebot-Enabled Website: Enhance Your Traffic with Smart Tracking</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Actualités <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Paul-Nizov-rejoint-ABBYY-au-poste-de-Chief-Information-Security-Officer"><a href="#Paul-Nizov-rejoint-ABBYY-au-poste-de-Chief-Information-Security-Officer" class="headerlink" title="Paul Nizov rejoint ABBYY au poste de Chief Information Security Officer"></a>Paul Nizov rejoint ABBYY au poste de Chief Information Security Officer</h2><p>20 avril 2021</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><ul><li>Paul Nizov sera en charge de la stratégie opérationnelle et budgétaire liée à la sécurité.</li><li>Paul Nizov dispose de plus de 15 ans d’expérience dans les domaines des technologies, du juridique et du militaire aux États-Unis, au Moyen-Orient et en Asie.</li><li>Paul a participé à la mise en place et à la gestion de programmes de cybersécurité dans les secteurs de l’énergie, de la finance, de la santé et des technologies.</li></ul><p>ABBYY, multinationale spécialisée dans l’intelligence digitale, annonce la nomination de Paul Nizov au poste de Chief Information Security Officer (CISO). Paul Nizov supervisera la stratégie opérationnelle et budgétaire liée à la cybersécurité. Il sera par ailleurs garant de la confidentialité et de la protection des données. Il s’agit d’une création de poste.</p><p><em>« La création de ce poste de CISO qui sera occupé par Paul Nizov est d’une importance capitale pour une entreprise technologique comme ABBYY. Nous sommes enthousiastes à l’idée de collaborer avec Paul qui sera le responsable de nos standards de sécurité pour le déploiement SaaS de nos solutions évolutives d’intelligence digitale. L’arrivée de Paul Nizov au sein de l’équipe dirigeante d’ABBYY reflète l’engagement que nous avons pris auprès de nos clients et de nos partenaires qui consiste à leur proposer des solutions pensées et développées selon les derniers principes de sécurité. La sécurité informatique ainsi que la confidentialité des données sont des considérations primordiales aujourd’hui. »</em>, souligne Ulf Persson, CEO d’ABBYY.</p><p>Paul rejoint ABBYY après avoir travaillé chez Ernst &amp; Young, où il était directeur général de la cybersécurité pour la région MENA. Durant ses quatre années au Moyen-Orient, Paul a travaillé avec des clients saoudiens et émiratis à la mise en place de technologies de cybersécurité visant à lutter contre les cybermenaces. Auparavant, Paul était chargé de la sécurisation des infrastructures stratégiques pour le compte de la Commission de réglementation nucléaire des États-Unis et pour Booz Allen Hamilton.</p><p><em>« Je suis ravi de rejoindre une entreprise reconnue pour ses innovations qui place la sécurité informatique au cœur de sa stratégie. Ma fonction au sein d’ABBYY sera stratégique. Le fait de collaborer étroitement avec l’équipe dirigeante et les équipes produit me permettra de maintenir au plus haut niveau la sécurité des solutions et des infrastructures d’ABBYY, et ce, afin de répondre aux besoins croissants de transformation des entreprises. »</em>, indique Paul Nizov.</p><p>Durant sa carrière, Paul a participé à la mise en place et à la gestion de programmes de cybersécurité au sein des secteurs des technologies de l’information et de la communication, de l’énergie, de la finance et de la santé. Il possède une expertise et une connaissance pointues en matière de conformité réglementaire (NIST, ISO, SOC, HITRUST, HIPAA et RGPD). Paul Nizov a notamment implémenté au sein de multiples entreprises des programmes permettant d’assurer la continuité des activités en temps de crise (gestion de crise et d’incidents).</p><p>Paul est titulaire d’un « Juris Doctor » obtenu à la SMU Dedman School of Law, d’une licence en génie électrique délivrée par l’Université du Texas à Dallas et de certifications en sécurité des systèmes d’information : CISSP et CISM. Paul est également vétéran de l’Armée américaine où il a servi dans la marine en tant qu’officier de sous-marin nucléaire. Dans le cadre de son service militaire, Paul a été diplômé de la Naval Nuclear Power School à Charleston, en Caroline du Sud, et du Naval Nuclear Prototype à Ballston Spa, dans l’État de New York.</p><p><strong>À propos d’ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY permet aux entreprises d’appréhender de manière précise leurs process et contenus via sa plateforme d’<a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >intelligence digitale <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Les technologies d’ABBYY équipent plus de 5 000 entreprises, dont un grand nombre figurent dans le classement Fortune 500. L’entreprise est reconnue pour ses solutions de pointe dans les domaines du <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Content Intelligence <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> et du <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Intelligence <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> qui ont pour vocation d’améliorer l’efficacité, la rentabilité et la compétitivité des entreprises ainsi que l’expérience client. ABBYY possède des bureaux dans 14 pays. Pour davantage d’informations, veuillez consulter le site <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/fr/" >https://www.abbyy.com/fr/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><strong>Contact presse:</strong></p><p>Bianca Stupp<br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >bianca.stupp@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>  </p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.nero.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=22889392&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="http://webstatic.nero.com/nero2015-com-wAssets/img/affiliate/media/banner728-90eng.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Cookiebot-Enabled-Website-Enhance-Your-Traffic-with-Smart-Tracking&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Cookiebot-Enabled-Website-Enhance-Your-Traffic-with-Sm</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://discover-advanced.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
